Why did you save me?
I thought I'd teach you something
about those bastards in the world of "ringers".
Akagi Shigeru!
Ron
If this goes on we'll lose
He wants to go "all or nothing" more than anyone.
That's Akagi's true nature.
That is the ONLY chink through which I can stab at him.
I'll aim there.
4th Game
South Round 2
Oh.
Kan.
Okaaay.
Tsumo.
Oh. 4 dora?
A Haneman win.
Haneman: 18,000/12,000 points dealer/non-dealer
Game 4
South Round 3
Akagi's luck has been running near 100%
He's in good shape for a Tsumo win.
The wall is overflowing with Akagi's winning draws.
Ten, what do you mean to do?
Riichi.
Pon.
The opposite of 100% luck is 0% luck.
your uncanny luck will be mine.
#/tv/shows sub par subs presents
**version**
Goro Takeshi as Ten Takeshi
Furukawa Yuki as Igawa Hiroyuki
Yoshida Eisaku as Akagi Shigeru
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(Ten: Nice guy on the path of Tenho)
Episode 4
Kan.
With that Pon call and the new draw order, the game flow changed instantly.
Again the 7 Man
What a terrifying draw.
It's probably Akagi's winning tile.
Discard the 4 Pin or this 7 Man.
If I do that...
Break up his hidden triplet or nothing else.
but now he's back to square one.
He's in Tenpai.
Now if only the game flow would come.
With that
could even Akagi lose?
Without doubt Akagi's game flow has moved to Ten.
Nah. I can't hold him off forever with this hand.
Another one, two turns maybe, but that's probably the limit.
Discard the 3 Pin?
If he's discarding only safe tiles he should choose the 6Man.
But he won't do that after coming so far.
What will you discard, Ten?
This character discarded a 6 Pin before
despite it being a dangerous tile
and he wasn't nervous at all.
That is to say he theorized it was safe.
That's a... WALL.
Wall: (壁 Kabe) A defensive strategy based on the unavailability of certain tiles.
A 3/6 Pin wall.
That is, this guy knows the location of at least 3 of the 4 Pin or 5 Pin tiles.
There's one 4 Pin out.
And I've got one.
This guy has either 2 4Pin or 3 5Pin tiles in his hand.
Then, what's he waiting for?
It's likely with two 4 Pin tiles he'll aim for an Iipeikou.
Iipeikou: A hand with one set of two sequences of the same numbers in the same suit. (here: 2Pin-2Pin-3Pin-3Pin-4Pin-4Pin)
If he gets a 4Pin he'd be waiting for a 3Pin.
Pon.
Ron.
Tanyao. 4 Dora.
Tanyao: Hand composed number tiles 2-8.
8,000 points.
3 7Mans, hun?
You catch on well.
A fine read.
Good discards.
Discards that show intention.
The consecutive Red Dragon discards, and discarding the dora.
With this are you going to close the 9,500 point gap in the final hand?
Well then...
You've got some fighting spirit, don't you.
If I play sluggishly I'll be dead.
Somehow, it seems like the wind is changing.
As I suspected.
Akagi's next draw was a 7Man!
He would have won on his next draw.
South Round 4
Last Hand
The points still stand at Akagi: 37,000 and Ten 27,500 .
Point difference: 9,500.
His starting hand is bad
but for Ten to pull off an upset
Ten must get at least 5,200 points this hand.
Pon.
Oh no. For no reason they're completing their hands fast.
That was a dangerous.
He skillfully passed it.
Pon.
This is another dangerous tile.
Wait a sec.
Akagi's doing that on purpose.
I see.
If the other guys win, Ten can't take the top spot.
Akagi will throw this hand.
Will he deal into one of their hands?
This guy's aiming for a White Dragon ToiToi
ToiToi: Hand composed of all triplets.
If he wins that's 5,200 points.
But, what to do about the dora?
If Akagi miscalculates and that guy has dora, it could utterly change he scoring.
There's even the chance of a Makura pair.
Makura: (枕) Antique term for the single pair in a completed hand.
There's one dora in the discards.
Oh, now I see!
Is Akagi holding the remaining 3 dora tiles?
Currently, in this hand
I have zero need to dwell on winning.
If I can't do it...
I'll have someone else tell me what to discard.
As I expected. This dummy.
Oh no.
If Akagi deals into that guy's hand, it's over.
Ron.
White dragon ToiToi.
5,200 points.
Fuck.
This is what Akagi was aiming for.
I've won this East-South round.
And.. how is that?
What?
I ALSO on that discard...
RON THE FUCK OUT OF YOU
Pinhu, Ipeikou.
2,000 points.
2,000?
B-but that isn't an upset.
No. But look at the points.
Shanyu? (Playoff round)
shānyū: (西入, entering the West). An extended West round when no player can exceed 30,000 points.
Certainly top rated Akagi dealt 5,200 points into that guy's hand.
and with Ten winning 2,000 points, he's at 29,500.
No one has reached 30,000 points.
I'd expect as much from a  Kantō ringer.
Kantō: The greater Tokyo area in western Japane.
Well judged.
Oi.
If my points in this extended round come beneath Ten
I'll forfeit the match.
W-what are you saying?
At best you'll be helping him.
He's baiting you.
You don't understand at all.
That which we're giving... and taking...
it isn't POINTS.
It's PRIDE.
West Round 1
Tsumo.
2,000 points from everyone.
Fuck yes!
That last moment double Ron in the previous game...
It changed the game flow.
West Round 1
First Honba.
Kan.
WHOOP THERE IT IS
4,100 points from everyone.
West round 3.
Riichi.
Ron.
8,000 points.
West Round 4
Final hand.
All things considered, Ten should come top this round.
If Akagi can't win with a Yakuman hand,
Yakuman:  The rarest and most valuable hands. 48,000/32,000 points for dealer/non-dealer.
He can't pull of an upset.
In the worst case Ten can play safe discards.
I can just glimpse victory.
From the first the possibility of DaiSanGen disappeared.
DaiSanGen, Kokusi Musou, Shousuushi etc. are all Yakuman valued hands.
Pon.
And with that the chance of Kokusi Musou is gone too.
Kan.
Now shousuushii, daisuushii, and tsuuiisou are gone.
Pon.
And now even ryuuiisou is gone.
Kan.
With that nearly every chance at a Yakuman hand is gone.
Things are going ideally.
No...
There's one avenue remaining.
Riichi.
If he's going to pull an upset, It can be nothing else.
Without doubt
Akagi has a single wait SuuAnKou.
SuuAnKou: 4 Hidden triplets
But... what is he waiting on?
Drawing an East Wind right after Akagi declares Riichi
It's tough to discard it considering the game flow, but Ten's 4 Sou triplet is also difficult to discard...
We're saved.
Ten has all four in his hand.
It's 100% certain to not be Akagi's hidden-triple single wait tile.
Ten has all but won.
So. The 4Man, hunh?
B-but that's not a SuuAnKou.
Then you haven't overtaken Ten's points!
No.
Ahh...
My hidden triplets are over THERE.
Ahhh...
First, 3 Ura-dora.
A Haneman hand.
and with this it's 6 Ura-Dora.
A Baiman hand.
t-that can't be.
Can he pull an upset?
If he turns over the same tile again, he'll have 9 Dora
An indesputable MATHEMATICAL Yakuman.
Akagi, where are you going?
I said it.
If I placed lower than Ten in this Round
I said I'd forfeit the match.
Y-ou can't
Thank you for your efforts.
Whoo hoo!
WE WON.
And now we celebrate!
Ten!
I haven't had such a hot blooded match
for a long, long time.
It's because of you
that I wanted to come back.
S-saved.
No, but
Seriously, 3 Ura-Dora?
There's literally no chance.
You're wrong.
When Akagi got up to leave
You didn't hear him, did you?
It went as he expected.
It's the next tile over.
The next tile?
The Akagi in his prime
Would have turned over all 3.
This was Akagi Shigeru's
SuuAnKou "Hell" wait.
Mere chance gave me the win.
It could just as well have been him, maybe.
Ten. Thanks for everything.
You saved me.
Please let me return the favor somehow.
Hiroyuki.
Stop this ringer business already.
Wha?
There's no problem with your Mahjong ability.
If you play a little longer
If you lose your natural innocence
I dunno, you just might be able to survive in this world
HOWEVER
just stop.
"Demons haunt the crossroads"
"Demons gather at the bones."
The bones are the tiles.
In this underworld...
there are any number of evil, powerful, brilliant characters...
They gather because of the tiles.
The world you ought to be in
it ain't this one.
I entered this damn place more than once,
and for me it's too late. I can't go back.
I have no choice but to live in this world.
HOWEVER
you can still turn back.
Later.
An underground Mahjong national competition.
This battle isn't for everyday, normal people.カタギ
This Mahjong is a struggle for life itself!
He's done the UNTHINKABLE.