And with that, the match is over!
What I just discarded was the 6th White Dragon !
Head bump?
This White Dragon Hiroyuki discarded wasn't a White Dragon at all
I declared Ron on
the missing tile that discard was destined to be
If there isn't a 5 Sou(bamboo) in that Mahjong case
the point penalty KNOCKS YOU THE FUCK OUT!
This swapped tile
was declared a 5 Sou by Akagi Shigeru when he decared Ron
There's a reason that isn't such a wild guess
You can read it off the discards
There's a reading?
Don't you remember?
In South round 1
Harada's hand
oh, yes
he declared Riichi on the 11th turn by discarding a 4 Sou (bamboo)
But in the end he didn't draw his tile.
The hand ended as a draw with Harada still in Tenpai
After the draw, his open hand showed he had 3 dora, a Mangan.
A 7 Sou edge wait
When you saw that hand, did anything cross your mind?
Just for a moment I thought...
discarding the 4 Sou to declare Riichi...
that was very strange
Keeping the 4 Sou...
and instead discarding the 8 Sou
then the 5 Sou wait would give an Ittsu with 3 Dora
Mangan without declaring Riichi
Clearly discarding the 5 Sou bothered him
Didn't it, though
throwing away a qualifying Yaku to instead declare Riichi
A most unlikely way to play
The reason why Harada played the way he did,
is he decided the chance of the Ittsu wait was extremely slim
At that time
perhaps, in Soga's hand...
There might have been a few 5 Sou
Naturally, he provided that information to Harada
he had that advantage
Well, I suppose that Harada just might also have known...
that there weren't four 5 Sou tiles
that in total, there were only 3...
Open the box
Do it
#/tv/shows subs presents
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takeshi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 9
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(Nice guy on the path of Tenho)
Well then...
As we expected, there's a fourth 5 tile inside
If so, it's in there.
There's a 5 Sou (bamboo)!
And the last one...
Okaay. Enough already
There's a 5 Pin there
Akagi was also waiting on a 5 Pin
That 5 Pin alone is enough. Case closed
B-but...
T-the FUCK?!?
The last one
the sole remaining tile
HUNH?
He got it wrong!
Akagi got it wrong!
No
His reading was flawless
Because Harada himself...
wanted to give it up half way through
That last tile
it really ought to have been a 5 sou
but in actuality it was 5 MAN
Harada had ordered the 5 Sou and 5 Pin swapped with White Dragons
but his underling mistook the order, not using a 5 Sou
instead swapping a 5 Man
A mistake like that, there's no way to predict it
B-but it doesn't matter!
Akagi was in fact waiting on a 5 Pin as well!
The win is confirmed. Harada said it himself!
It doesn't matter. Akagi's win is complete!
Okay. Enough already!
Harada said it himself! Akagi has survived
Hiroyuki...
It's all one
What Harada says has nothing to do with it
I declared a Ron on a 5 Sou
And the missing tile wasn't a 5 Sou
To me, the result is all that matters
I don't need it. Winning like that
Akagi!
Harada
It's been a while since I've been here
Was fun
Akagi is a most interesting man
But no one is in Tenpai!
The contest isn't over yet
The day of the final will be changed
and the rules revised
both teams can suggest new ones
Agreed
For all of us, after all this,
What in the world becomes of us?
As I'm a human being I will perish
and return to the earth
And then, after how many thousands of years,
we're reborn as something else
Maybe as microbes spread throughout in the sea
to be eaten by some faggy fish
or maybe as some whelp,
or a bird
I don't really care when I die
because life is reborn
but the one thing that bothers me
when I, as a human being, drop dead
is this feeling of who I am
that consciousness will vanish
What really scares me
is becoming what I'm not
And for that, I'm sorry
Can you understand?
Should I win,
or should I fail,
It's Akagi Shigeru who won...
or lost
Whatever Harada does is of no consquence
I decided that tile was a 5 Sou
and the tile itself wasn't a 5 Sou
that's the sole thing that's important
Ten,
It's up to you now
Day of the East/West Final
Ten,
Can I ask you something?
If it had been you,
would you have done the same as Akagi?
I remain
because if you don't remain, you can't win
Remain
I'm me. You're you.
Akagi is Akagi.
No one lives the same
Here and now,
you and I have survived this far
and that is everything
And what's more
I, above all else,
concentrate wholeheartedly on victory
and to that end I'll suggest a certain rule to the West team
a rule which can best play to your logical nature
Mr. Ten, we've been waiting for you.
This way please
"Clear" Mahjong?
What is that?
It's a Mahjong team variant that does without trading points
It's a rule which awards victory to the team who clears 5 agreed upon Yaku
The Yaku one must clear...
are certain 2 Han Yaku
Ittsu, Sansyoku, Chanta, Chtoitsu, SanAnKou
Calling tiles is allowed
Are you joking?
There's no reason why we have to agree to a foolish game like that!
Quiet!
It's fine. We agree
And your side?
The normal point system,
If a member goes bankrupt, that team loses.
So it's not just pure luck
Well, then
You're okay playing with both these rules together?
Fine
Proposing an idiotic rule like that
is proof enough they're cornered
The Yaku which must be cleared...
can largely be separated into two groups
the first group, because it's a team game, offers protection against direct hits
East Round 1
they are mobile, quick Yaku
for which you can call tiles
these are Ittsu, Sansyoku, and Chanta
And on the other hand...
there are laborious Yaku which you must construct on your own
namely, Chitoitsu and SanAnKou
specifically, of all five, SanAnKou is the biggest hurdle
You might say it has the number one level of difficulty
Pon
A single suit hand？
Kan
The South team knows full well that SanAnKou is the key to Clear Mahjong.
So If I declare a closed Kan,
to the contrary, they ought to imagine I don't see the true worth a SanAnKou
Soga's going for a Chinisou?
But if I declare a 2nd closed Kan
as you'd expect, they'll perceive I'm aiming for a SanAnKou
Chii
Got it!
A confirmed SanAnKou
There's only two 3 Sou tiles left
a terrible wait,
but if Hiroyuki has a 3 Sou
and deals it into my hand,
my SanAnKou is complete
Hiroyuki,
Do you have any 3 Sou?
I don't have any
What Sou tiles do you have?
5 Sou, 7 Sou, 9 Sou
After that, 1 Man
Can he deal into my hand at all?
As far as that's concerned
there's merely two tiles left on this 3/6 wait
just waiting for a win is almost impossible
Without doubt he's got a Sou single suit hand
Anyone can clearly see this from his two exposed calls
There's a danger he's on a 4 or 5 Sou double sided wait
HOWEVER
this is the path I must take
Chi
If I deal into his hand the risk of a foolish Haneman or Baiman hit is huge
HOWEVER
Risk and Return are two sides of the same coin
Into the jet black darkness of the game
you have to stick your hand into the terrifying deeps
It... passed
Afterwards, all Hiroyuki must do is deal in with his 5 Sou
Judging merely by that Red Dragon
he ought not be discarding dora which are likely to complete Soga's Chinisou
He's in tenpai for a huge hand
A SanAnKou?
If I leave it be for one turn
and the kid deals into it, it's over
One moment now
Kan
Kan!
When Harada flipped those two Dora indicators
Swapping in tiles from his hand, he gave Ten's hand two Dora
With his Red Dragon Kan, it's a SanBaiMan hand
As the point value is so high, no one can deal into it
We survived
If the kid were to deal into that
he'd only have 1000 points left
pretty much an act of suicide
and thus Ten's SanAnKou is no more
Afterwards Soga will collect a 4 Sou
or I'll complete my hand and knock you out
no problem
Come on, kid. I took this hand last turn
that's crazy!
Anyway, Ten won't even accept that direct hit
Is that the way it is?
Well, if that's your gut feeling
it's okay then
I'll take it
Ron
24,000 points
and SanAnKou has been cleared
West Team:
Harada: 25000 Soga: 25000
East Team:
Ten: 49000 Hiroyuki: 1000
this is an expression of our determination
Without averting our eyes from hard facts,
embrace each crisis while moving forward,
Opening the way
SanAnKou
Chitoitsu
Chanta
SanSyoku
Ittsu
East Round 2
An awful starting hand, well beyond saving
If he discards a South wind, the hand will not continue
How do you retreat from such a position?
Advance!