Tenho Street
Riichi Mahjong Minami
This building,2nd floor
Ron.
8 Thousand points
Again!?
No.
I learned probability at university.
Incident?
There are a total of 136 tiles in Mahjong.
There's a 3% chance of drawing the tile you want.
And that's it.
Well, I've had enough.
Who'll play next?
Ten, your noodles are ready.
Ten!
Can't you see what I'm doing?
Right now,
I'm eating yakisoba.
Have you ever eaten it yourself?
the yakisoba at this place
is the best on the planet.
Okay. Okay. I get it. On the planet.
What kind of guy is it?
He's as precise as a computer. No weaknesses.
Proprietor. Thanks.
Thank you Ten.
Ron.
5100 points.
Shit.
Looks like I've got to quit.
Oh, you'r sure winning ain't you.
Will you play me?
Based on Ten: Tenhou-doori no Kaidanji by Fukumoto Noboyuki
Goro Takeshi as Ten Takeshi
Furukawa Yuki as Igawa Hiroyuki
Yoshida Eisaku as Akagi Shigeru
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(Blessed Way of the Nice Guy Ten)
I'm confident anything will be fine. But...
How about a side bet.
A side bet?
If I win, you give back what you won from everyone.
I don't need any money.
And if you lose?
I double your winnings.
Yeah. I guess.
I've been wanting to meet someone like you.
Well then it's decided.
At the table over there?
A non-automatic table must be so he can cheat.
That's got to be it.
If he didn't do that he wouldn't be sure to beat someone he doesn't know.
You can stack tiles by hand, can't you?
Yeah.
No problem.
East Round 1
The contest is one East South round, and whoever has more points wins, even if its merely 100 more.
First I have to make sure there's no cheating.
I can't do a single wait on an undiscarded tile, but...
Riichi.
Ron.
12,000 points.
South Round 1
Ron.
8,000 points.
What's with this character? The silent type.
South Round 2
Pon.
Ron.
12,000 points.
Even a novice wouldn't deal into that.
All that remains is this guy's turn as dealer.
But I'm in the lead by 50,000 points.
Just what is he playing at?
Ah the power went out.
S-sorry. I hit the switch with my elbow.
Ten. It's your turn.
Ah. I've got this.
Tenhou Chuuren PouTou
(Nine gates completed on Dealer's first tile draw)
He did it!
Typical Ten. It's a complete reversal of 90,000 points!
This is not possible. You cheated.
Will you admit it?
Oh yes.
Mahjong
is a truly fearsome thing isn't it?
Just hold on a second.
Admit you cheated.
Cheat?
Aren't you, a pro, embarrassed to do something so childish?
A sneaky underworld guy like you
And what's your name?
Name.
Igawa Hiroyuki.
Well, then.
Be it sneaky, or cheating...
I have to win by any means necessary.
Are you happy to win such a low victory?
Can you be content playing the Mahjong of a charlatan?
That
is being a Pro.
It's regrettable,
The sweet world you imagine is very far from the truth.
You're no use.
I watched your Mahjong very closely.
In that match, Ten did cheat.
You won.
Shall you try once more?
Excuse me.
Oh Sawada! Please, please.
The player for this time
Player?
Boy, he's a young one.
I've seen him play.
Ah. What's this about?