Won't you play me?
Wha--? Is it a blackout?
Tenhou Chuuren Poutou
He cheated!
The contest is 5 games.
It's completely a bluff.
Well then. Round 2.
Let's begin, shall we?
Game 2 East Round 2
Ten/Nakanishi Team 1 Victory
Riichi.
Their side has the game flow.
Little by little I can see their strategy.
Ron.
6,500 points.
What the hell you doing?
Game 2
South Round 1
Riichi.
As I thought. It's the single color tile strategy they used in the first game.
They've varied the pattern.
Nakanisi has declared Riichi when he's not in Tenpai...
And Ten is waiting for his discarded tiles.
I get it.
I won't deal into his hand any more!
The meaning of Nakanishi declaring Tempai is then...
If I follow Ten's discards I should be safe.
This tile will pass.
This should pass as well.
Ron.
Hunh?
8,000 points. Alright!
I can't read what those guys are aiming at.
No.
It's not that at all.
What are you thinking?
I noticed some telling looks between Ten and Nananishi.
Earlier, when I dealt into Nakanishi's hand...
Nakanishi was very pleased.
Ten was flustered.
With that. Some mistake was made.
Some cooperation between them was broken, I think.
We take advantage of it.