Two player Mahjong
I declare Tenpai
It's difficult to imagine a Man tile wait off Ten's discards
How about that
A Baiman hand!
Damn!
To flip the game Ten needs to make a Mangan or greater hand
Ten minutes remain
When the next bell rings...
the hand we're in is the last one
Tenpai!
What's Harada waiting on?
THIS
To wait in the most unexpected place of all!
Let it be in time!
This hand is the FINAL BATTLE
There's a 11,100 point difference between them
For Ten to win...
It's come
If he draws a Red Dragon with Riichi
A Riizumo with Red and White Dragons is a Mangan
He's broken through
If he plays with all his ability, it's unavoidable!
Harada's one sided wait
Only a little time remains
He can't discard this middle wait
As far as that's concerned
West wind is the one to throw out
Pon
With that move a Yaku is confirmed
Afterwards, no matter the tiles, it's best just to get into Tenpai
It's over
Ten has two limitations strangling him
One is making a Mangan hand or greater
The other is his hand being read in stage B
To that goal he needs godly luck
Harada's one tile from Tenpai
This character...
he can sense my hidden 8 Pin triplet
If I discard a 3 Man in this state...
Or, perhaps...
If I discard the 2 and 4 Sou
What a mistake!
If he kept the 4 Sou and discarded the 3 Man, he'd be in Tenpai!
Harada's gut instincts...
have they been washed away?
T-Ten!
It's getting more difficult
Hiroyuki...
It's fine
Harada's also having a tough time
He hasn't gotten into Tenpai despite calling that West Wind
And what's more...
Ten's one tile from Tenpai!
Draw your tile!
Shit!
Come on!
There's no time!
If you don't win this...
Victory is right before me
I have to struggle onwards to a Mangan
And to do that...
I can't possibly call that 2 Sou
HOWEVER
My Instinct is telling me to
Such a price
reatreat is also difficult
It's the same as an advantage
It's difficult
the possibility...
Don't abandon it
to the absolute end...
to Victory!
Chii
Ten played it!
A final unbelievable gamble!
Harada
this is it
I declare it
Tenpai
I win Stage A
But I'm not through yet
to the bitter end
That call is his Achillies Heel
Calling that tile...
Riichi, Ippatsu, Tsumo, and Ura-Dora all became impossible
That is to say...
He's got to struggle to a Mangan
Compared with reading a closed hand, it's overwhelmingly easier
That call...
and those discards...
from those two it's possible to deduce his Yaku
Otherwise with two Honor triplets he's got a Chanta with one Dora
But with some luck...
he might have two dora
He certainly doesn't have a hidden Dora triplet
Red and White Dragons with a Dora pair
his wait is some kind of double sided wait
More than that, first...
I need to be cautious
It's HERE
The hell is he doing?
It's a winning tile...
but I choose not to win with it
HA HA HA HA HA
To lesiurely let it pass
He's lost it
He can't draw it!
To the bitter end...
The game flow's with ME
As exptected
You think you'll get two chances at your 5 draws?
You've lost it
I won't give you another chance!
First off, letting that win pass...
He's got two or more winning tiles
Considering his discards...
If he draws a 1 Sou it's a Chanta Mangan
And if he drew the lower scoring 4 Sou
he'd let it pass
Anyhow, these two types of hands
Just two types without doubt
This!
this?
What in hell has he done?
Okay
The bastard's discards...
10 tiles and he didn't draw his winning tile
and I've chosen 4 tiles
Furthermore, with my discards...
and my hand itself
among Honisou combinations...
there's but one left
arranged like so
Take this!
Idiot
No.
Wait a second
That call
Chanta with Honors and 1 Dora
and furthermore a SanSyoku!
That's a Mangan
I have it!
Ten's wait is a 1 or 2 Pin
WITHOUT DOUBT
Kan
OH FUCK
On a Rinshan replacement draw?!?
Idiot
The probability of that is zero
All the new 9 Pin Dora are out
There's none in Ten's hand
And now there's no way for Ten to get a Mangan
I'VE WON
N-no
WAIT A MOMENT...
A Red Dragon closed Kan...
You're right Harada
because It didn't give me the conditions for a Mangan
HOWEVER
Now
Ten
and with this very thing
HARADA
It's been a loong time coming!
The game is over
Red, White Dragon and 1 Dora
Mangan
*Fuhane
*Fuhane (符跳ね): Scoring 12 or more fu points, causing the score to reach the 40 point level
That Red Dragon closed Kan is 32 Fu points
it's more than 61 Fu points
that is to say, it's beyond Fu point reckoning
at the absolute minimum it qualifies as a Mangan
s-shit
Ten
Tell me one thing
between White and Red dragon...
only one of each remained
HOW did you bet on that probability?
Harada
That wasn't probability
There weren't any Red or White Dragons in your discards
you also had none
That is to say...
I thought they remained in the wall
In this Two Person Mahjong...
If my winning tile wasn't read
I could be devoted to drawing the tile
In other words...
Whichever I drew between Red and White Dragon I could declare a closed Kan with
I could see this
and you could not
Of course,
Those White and Red Dragons...
was in the wall
It was deeper...
MY reality
compared to YOUR reality
Simply put...
that's all it was
I've lost