"Clear" Mahjong?
Designated yaku
The team that clears them first, wins
If that's your gut feeling
It's okay.
I'll take it
Ron.
SanAnKou cleared
I missed a pair?
Could I get a chitoitsu like this?
The alternative is a called Tanyao
Chii
Pon
Shit!
My chance gone in one moment
Soga's without doubt in Tenpai
According to his discards...
his wait is most probably
a 3, 6 Pin wait
I'm in Tenpai
But, it's one step too late
If I had reached Tenpai just one turn earlier
Ten could have dealt me a 6 Pin
but in the current situation
a 6 Pin is Soga's winning tile
He'd Head Bump
Dealing in is impossible
やつは今
Even now the little guy
しくじりながらも懸命になんとかしようとしている
despite failure, he's trying his utmost
その意気に賭けよう
I'll bet on his determination
There's most probably still one 6 Pin left in the wall
He got it
With that last draw the Kid's hand is ready
If you consider his Chitoitsu fell apart...
he's waiting on this very 6 Pin or a 9 Pin
but now he's aiming for a Tanyao
and at this moment he can't win off a 6 Pin
according to his discards, Ten certainly has a 6 Pin
But he's read Soga's wait
and he can't deal into it
and I just drew the 4th 6Pin!
The kid's Tanyao is nipped in the bud
The only remaining ways he could win
is winning off the last draw or the last discard
I'll erase those hopes as well!
Chii
Take that
I've cheated you of a final draw win
now your win is bugger all
It's over
there's two more turns
but this hand is already done
If I discard the 9 Pin I'm in Tenpai
9 Pin is one of the kid's winning tiles
but outside calling it on the final discard
the moron's got no Yaku
therefore If I get into Tenpai
In this hand, the kid...
will end up with a no Tenpai penalty
1,500 or possibly decreased to 1,000 points
it's over if that happens in his current state
the kid's already dead if he deals into a hand
If that happens
I'll blow him away with a Tsumo
If that happens losing 500 points is huge
Pon
He's still holding onto those?
The last draw which I took pains to give to Soga
Is with that kid again!
there's no more 6 Pin tiles to draw
He's aming to draw the final 9 Pin, isn't he!
Kan
A Rinshan replacement draw?
at any rate
it's all the same if he's betting on a single draw
That possibility is paper thin
It's only natural
the natural outcome
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
実ったぞ
The fruit has ripened
はい
I understand
ripened?
what's he on about?
Kan
OH FUCK
Yes...
dealing into a hand doesn't have to come from the discards
Ron
ChanKan, 3 Dora
8,000 points
the FUCK did I do...?
Pon
Ten's 9 Pin Pon call
It wasn't a Pon call when he had two tiles
It was a Pon call when he had THREE
Then the Kid, from Ten's hand
took the remaining 9 Pin!
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
生き延びたな
You survived
Yes, I did
Now Hiroyuki has a safety buffer
an overwhelming advantage
FUCK SHIT PISS
Chii
Ron!
Ittsuu clear
Tsumo
Chitoitsu
Runnn
Ron
Ittsuu
TSUMO!
Chanta!!!
The game's going back and forth
but as I thought
Ten's initial win
that SanAnKou
After they clear a Chanta and Sansyoku
if that happens...
it's ZA ENDO
The time that remains...
there's only a little left
5 or 6 hands
No...
less than 2 or 3
damn SanAnKou
If I complete a similar SanAnKou...!
Got it!
Chii
Pon
Ten's fast
If he can discard a 7 Sou he'll clear SanSyoku
In this situation he's simply got to discard the 7 Sou
He's somehow in Tenpai, isn't he
There's a good chance his wait is above 6 Pin
Is it Chanta hand?
He's got it!!!
If he discards the 8 Pin he's in Tenpai for a SanAnKou
but it's likely that's the tile the other side is waiting for
I clearly can't win waiting for an 8 Pin
If I complete this hand...
with merely a double South Wind it's only 3,200 points
and there ain't many turns left
Kan
you CLOWN
舐めた真似しよって
He's making like he's given up!
Calling Kan on 9 Pin and discarding his 8 Pin
he passed on the 8 Pin I discarded
this little act of yours
I'll make him regret it!
His hand isn't becoming a SanAnKou
but a Pinhu, Ipeikou, 2 Dora hand is Mangan
According to his dicards harada's aiming for SanAnKou
and Ten a Chanta
they're both ignoring faster winning hands!
the idea of "clearing" hands is of more advantage
oh shiiii
And with this...
RON
AND SANANKOU CLEARED
やられた
He's done for
万全を尽くした天さんが敗れ、
Ten thought he covered all possibilities, but still lost
一鉄を通した原田が勝った
Harada's Ironclad persistence paid off
すでにこの場は通常の定石確率は通用しない
by-the-book probabilities are already useless in a game like this
An absolutely terrible starting hand
Chii
A SanSyoku?
h-he's fast!
間に合うのか
まずい、差し込まれたか
原田の手の速さを見たら欲張らず三色だけでも和了っておくべき。まだ原田は聴牌していない。天さんの待ちは恐らく索子の下辺り、天さんがツモるか俺が差し込めればこの局は勝てる
そうか、原田の三色、そもそもあれが目くらまし。やつらは三色など鼻から眼中にない
点棒で俺を脱落させるつもりだったんだ
こいつら
なんて事考えやがる
ちっ、気付いたか
きりそうな気配だったのに
よくぞ気付いた。ひろゆき
こいつら、
またせこい手を使いやがって
今は最終局面、
どんな手を使っても
勝たなきゃいかんのや
そのリーチ、
後悔させたるわ