TENHO CHUUREN POUTOU
We win.
Be a ringer for me once more
A chitoitsu.
(all pairs hand)
He turns down each pair when he's got one?
How did he read my discards?
Interesting game you're having there, isn't it
Won't you let me mix it up too?
Hiroyuki,
Change with me
You...
you can't beat this boomer
My playing...
won't be a problem, will it?
N-no
I'm thankful with all my heart for what you're doing, Ten
What is this changing shit?
Seriously,
I ain't afraid
(Kansai dialect)
2nd Game
East Hand 1
Again?
How does he have such faith that he'll complete his hand?
It looks like he's extremely confident
I start playing and after some hours...
I can read the way the tiles are flowing
My Chitoitsu hands have been called amazing
This sense of mine
this is what people have said
Ron.
A Chitoitsu
Yet another Chitoitsu?
How can he win in this uncanny way?
2nd Game
East Hand 3
Ten
I can lay down my triplets as I complete them too
There's no reason you have to be the only one...
showing your hand's progress
Bro
Don't underestimate me
I'm not in Tenpai.
I'm not either
#/tv/shows Hit or miss I guess they never miss huh TikTok|1 HOUR LOOP
presents:
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takeshi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 3
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice Guy on Tenho Way)
2nd Game
East Hand 4
Again
Ten is trying to provoke Murota and destroy his pace, but...
this style of playing, it's Murota's specialty
Ten is entering his opponent's home turf,
and explicitly asking for a contest
He's already in Tenpai.
As I thought, he's like a monster
What tile is he waiting on?
The dora is Red Dragon
He's probably holding low Sou tiles?
No matter how you put it, this is...(dangerous)
It passed!
This passed too!?!
You've guessed it haven't you, Hiroyuki?
A facade
Indeed. A facade
This character's Mahjong...
is the Mahjong of "giving up"
The weapon he uses in making players give up is merely his image
Making himself out to be a monster or a god...
to make players fold, he applies pressure
but still only progresses at his own pace
But when I did the same thing
his own pace started to freeze
I dare say
Those pairs you've laid down...
They're make believe.
They aren't all pairs at all
You're reckless
Ron
TanYao, SanSyoku
(Only tiles 2-9, from 3 suits)
7,700 points
Y-you..
You ought not have been in Tenpai!
You think I'm so fucking dumb I'd tell you the composition of my hand?
You've been playing in such a profoundly dishonest way...
you shouldn't be trusting anyone, should you?
So, let's continue, shall we?
2nd Game
South Hand 4
He's got it
He's in Tenpai
Kan
At this point he's discarded a 1 and 2 Pin
He was aiming for a SanSyoku or Tanyao
(3 Suits, or only tiles 2-8)
But he gave up on them...
That is to say...
This guy's got an extra 4 Pin
That end tile there is the extra 4 Pin
Ten followed it with his eye
Humph.
He just now deliberately followed that tile with his eye
Does he think that'll make me feel safe and discard MY 4 Pin or something?
A PERFECT draw!
But he can't discard his 4 Pin
Ten to one, Murota is waiting on it
T-ten! That's the tile Murota's waiting for!
He dealt into Murota's hand
That tile is a 4 Pin!
How?
I could have sworn...
He ought to have drawn the 4 Pin
H-how?
Certainly, just now...
The jerk dew that very tile!
How was that tile not a 4 Pin?!?
This Dora tile will be tough to discard
Do I break up a pair?
But that's like confessing I'm not on a single wait
How about this?
Yes.
That 8 Sou I thought was a 4 Pin
H-he ought not be waiting on it!
At last... you look up
TanYao with one Dora.
3,900 points
Of course
You've done it Ten
Ten DID pick up his 4 Pin
But in that instant he switched it for the 8 Sou he just drew
It wasn't a cheat
It was all within his own hand
As I thought. His Mahjong is strong
That's as far as it goes
You probably won't be winning any more
You yourself have... "given up"
You retreated from a difficult position...
and you couldn't read your OWN mind
It's true all the world round...
Those who crumble under pressure
have no path to victory
What will you do?
Won't you show this guy out?
I already said
I'm retired
The chairman is constrained for time
Would you somehow...?
No way
I don't have the stamina for long matches any more
Murota just lost.
There's no one else but you
Murota
What kind of guy beat him?
Some guy named Ten
Ten
It looks like they'll change a player for the next East South game
I see
Can I ask you something?
Ten, even though you were my opponent,
why did you help me?
I thought I'd teach you something in front of "Hama-chan"
something about ringers and the REAL world of Mahjong
Time to start again
AKAGI SHIGERU
Why HIM?
Is his Mahjong Strong?
"Strong" isn't a sufficient word for what he is
During his career no one has been able to defeat him
Without doubt...
a man with the innate ability to blow others away
Until this day he hasn't lost a single game
A PEERLESS Mahjong professional
Mahjong professional
Are you Ten?
Y-you know of me?
Rumors... on the wind
Haven't you retired?
I heard about a strong player
It's been a long time
but I thought I'd try to play him
3rd Game
East Hand 1
Akagi Shigeru
How on earth will he play?
Pon
Chii
Amazing.
It's only just started,
but already the game's coming to a boil
Simply put, it's not just his speed,
The man himself exudes a strange atmosphere
It's indescribable, like something in the air
Brilliance
A brilliance that suggests a further vast capacity for brilliance
This man is overflowing with the strange and unknown
Ron
Chanta with Red Dragon
Chanta...
Chanta: All triples and pairs must contain a terminal tile [1 or 9] or honor[dragon or wind]
and finished on only the 4th turn?
I can't get my hand moving in only 4 turns
Really?
You three guys have discarded 9 tiles
I drew 2 of those
All told, It felt like I drew eleven times
3rd Game
East Hand 3
Pon
Tsumo
Another Chanta?
3rd Game
East Hand 4
I'm not in Tenpai
Tenpai
Not his typical consecutive wins...
but once again he was going for a Chanta hand
Isn't it about time you play in a more normal style?
No. This will be fine
I'm still measuring him
Measuring?
The Mahjong I'm playing now does not depend upon luck
In a 100 games...
it'll win 100
Without knowing the general strength of your opponent
jumping in head first wouldn't do
3rd Game
South Hand 2
Riichi
Ron
That's not Chanta
Well, I thought i'd swtich it up some
3rd Game
South Hand 3
Welp, sorry. I haven't got any honor tiles
Riichi
A... code?
Well done
If no one noticed I wouldn't know what I'd do
It would be sad playing with three worthless players
Code?!?
What's he talking about?
Hiroyuki, you understand by now, don't you
Up to now Akagi's hands have been largely Chanta, right?
He told us which in his discards
The orientation of discarded honor tiles
Upside down means Chanta
Tsumo
Riichi
Right side up means it's not Chanta
Well then. This time it's Chanta
Are you an idiot?
Ron
But that's...
Shut the fuck up, bitch
You're just embarrassing yourself by talking
Now, Ten...
he stopped himself before declaring Riichi
B-but you turned the character tile!
That depends on the situation
Before, when Akagi discarded the 9 Man
I don't have any honor tiles
If you think of the 9 Man as an honor tile, it was upside down, meaning Chanta
But, strictly speaking, 9 Man is not an honor tile
So therefore you could think it won't be chanta as well
You can see that at first glance...
but you'll understand when you look at Akagi's open hand
If he won with a 1 Sou he'd have Chanta
with a 4 Sou and it wouldn't be Chanta
That is to say he was waiting on BOTH outcomes and discarded accordingly
That kid watching from the sidelines understands
You've therefore been playing with trash, haven't you Ten?
3rd Game
South Hand 4
I'm a bit hungry
Would you get me something good?
Is sushi okay?
Sushi, hunh?
You guys...
The most delicious thing in the world...
what is it?
Normal people probably say it's fugu or sushi
It ain't that
For example, when you play Mahjong
There are those who will bet their entire fortune...
betting on one big play like they're omnipotent...
playing with tiles cut from their very souls
A tile with a soul riding on it
When you call "Ron" on such a tile...
It feels like you're devouring their heart... their soul
Compared to that flavor...
fugu or sushi are as good as garbage
In this world...
people's souls are the most delicious thing of all
Riichi
Ron
Baiman
(24,000 points direct hit)
We're in a tough spot
It can be perfectly summed up:
We're going to lose like this
No.
Akagi just now...
I could see an opening once or twice
He progresses with a near perfect game...
HOWEVER
Deep inside he's thinking this is a load of shit
Shit
What he wants most of all isn't winning by staring off into space
Akagi's heart...
is he wants a real fight
He want's to go "all or nothing" more than anyone else.
This is Akagi's true nature
That is the ONLY chink through which I can stab the bastard
I'll aim there
The opposite of 100% is 0%.
Your uncanny luck will be MINE
Preview
What we're playing for isn't points...
It's PRIDE