Camouflage before Riichi
That's a Mahjong PREREQUISITE
Hiroyuki,
He's TRANSFORMED
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 7000 Mitsui: 5000
Soga: 13000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 9
South Hand 2
The Kid's getting carried away
I won't let MY weakness be seen either
Riichi
So, If I declare Riichi I've got a Mangan, hunh?
No. It would be useless
If I get carried away and declare Riichi, I'll deal into a Mangan
And then it's all over
Riichi
And there it is
Ten's in Tenpai too
There it is!
Soga's winning tile
Ehhh?
He won't take it?!?
Why did he let the win pass?
He passed even though a direct hit off Ten...
would be Mangan with an Ura-Dora
Is this it?
Mentanpin Tsumo
Aaaand
any additional Ura-dora?
FUCK YES
A Mangan hand
It can't be
Soga could have won off Ten's 7 Pin discard
This is unthinkable
He purposefully waited after passing on my discard
His goal:
To cut down Hiroyuki's points
If Hiroyuki falls to just 1000 points
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 1000
Akagi: 12000
West Team
Harada: 5000 Mitsui: 5000
Soga: 13000 Akutsu: 11000
then neither I nor Akagi can declare Tsumo anymore
He decided that was preferable
And persistently sought a Tsumo
#/tv/shows Esto El Fin El Grande Padre oy pesentamos:
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Kishitani Goro
Ten Takeshi
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Furukawa Yuki
Igawa Hiroyuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 8
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(Nice guy on Tenho Way)
Game 10
East Hand 1
Harada is most probably holding a Pinzu (dots) Honisou
So here, should he discard his 7 Sou (bamboo)?
If he discards the 7 Sou he's one from Tenpai
Harada's still full of Pin (dot) tiles
If he's careless he may yet deal into Hiroyuki's hand
Only a Tatehon hand?(closed single suit)
This won't amount to a Mangan hand
It gets him to Tenpai one turn faster
However
If Hiroyuki draws a 1 or 4 Pin, he might just discard it
Looks like Harada's in Tenpai
If he wins then the loss to this side should be large
If Hiroyuki had discarded a 7 Sou from this hand
He'd be in Tenpai now with this 1 Pin draw
He missed the win, didn't he
No
It wasn't a mistake at all
hunh?
This hand,
Will change into an entirely DIFFERENT one
A *Junchan **Ryanpeikou???
*Junchan: All sets contain a terminal [1 or 9]
**Ryanpeikou: Two double sequences (here 2x 7, 8, 9 Sou, 2x 1, 2, 3 Pin)
but to get that you'd need to draw another 9 Sou, and he's already using 3!
If you could draw someting like that it would be the DEVIL'S OWN LUCK
He's truly got no chance
My god...
H-he DREW IT
So, now they change
Whether this hand will be completed is now entrusted to Ten
This is bad
Ten's discards show he's certainly got a large hand
Alright!
Ipeikou Tsumo with 2 Dora
A Mangan win
Hiroyuki,
I'm sorry
Let me get a little crazy here
I've had a vision
of a pounding within the earth
of a DRAGON
sunk deep underground
Kan
His hand's all messed up
His chance for either Jyunchan or Ryanpeiko just vanished!
Why?
Akutsu is without doubt in Tenpai
If he wins he could take out the East team
Jesus H. Christ
A typical slow SuuAnKou
Is it no use at all?
Kan
THE DRAGON HAS SPLIT THE EARTH
Tsumo
SuuAnKou
He did it!
This SuuAnKou lowers Akagi's score by 8,000 points
but the other two are KNOCKED OUT AT ONE STROKE
The path from the initial hand to that SuuAnKou was quite narrow and treacherous
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 1000
Akagi: 4000
West Team
Harada: 5000 Mitsui: disqual
Soga: 13000 Akutsu: disqual
HOWEVER
at the very end of that path
was a way to FLIP THE GAME
The east as the flow..
don't they
Now, now. it's still okay
Akagi and Hiroyuki are only just BARELY in the game
With one hit and we can kick them...
YOU MORON(kansai dialect)!!!
What is this fucking mealy mouthed SHIT!
Understand what that win means!
They put it all on the line
It's got NOTHING to do with their fucking POINTS!
Soga,
I've already decided what we have to do
It's okay, isn't it?
As you like
More and more this looks like the last hand, doesn't it
Ten's SuuAnKou just now
It lit a fire under their asses
They're gonna come at us with everything they got
This isn't any reasonable contest any more
Will we eat or be eaten?
This is a battle of base instinct
Everything you got
NO HOLDS BARRED
10th Game
South Hand 1
Riichi
It's come
The first Riichi of the last hand
Is a Mangan hand
If he draws his tile, it's over
My making a quick hand is best here
but this hand's a slow one as well
This game doesn't have a "no tenpai penalty"
So I just have to not deal into his hand
SHIT
It wasn't an Itsuu
An end wait on 7 Sou?
Why on earth?
10th Game
South Hand 3
Come on!
I'm in Tenpai
If I discard the 5 Pin it's a 1/4 Pin wait
Or if I discard the 3 Pin it's a 2 Pin/White dragon two-pair wait
Whatever I do my two White Dragons are Dora, plus an Iipeikou
and If I Riichi it's certainly more than Mangan
As there's already two White Dragons discarded...
so my decision is straightforward
Riichi
With such a readable wait
I won't be able to get a direct hit
Naturally the West team won't deal into it
But I wasn't expecting that from the start
I WILL DRAW IT
IT CAN'T BE!
FIVE white dragon tiles???
It's the west team
The West team mixed in an extra White from the start
But... for what purpose?
Is it insurance?
If you're at a disadvantage, just announcing there's 5 white tiles...
will invalidate the hand
You've got to be kidding
There's no reason why I have to play along with this
BUT, why should I throw away my advantage?
If I complete my hand, I win
If I draw it I WIN
South and North wind tiles?
I can understand him playing around my Riichi
but having a North and South wind floating in your hand so late in the game is unusual
A Kokusi Musou?
Yeah, more and more it's looking that way
Still, it is amusing
He may be in tenpai but I can't lose if he's waiting on a White Dragon that will never come
I've got the other two he's waiting for
Even if Harada thinks there's two remaining
It's just impossible for him to get one
And if it's impossible, the chances he deals into my hand increases
More and more this White Dragon
looks like a poison mixed in to benefit Harada
and ironically that poison
is now running through Harada's own veins
Any moment now...
A SIXTH WHITE DRAGON???
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE FUCKING KIDDING
Enough with the fucking cheating already
Whats the matter?
If it doesn't complete your hand get rid of it, or else...
have you forgotten how to discard?
OH, a White Dragon?
Well, then...
Ron!
Kokusi Musou
HA HA HA HA HA!
And with that, the game is over!
Stop fucking around,
I'm not going to accept a game like this!
LOOK!
What I discarded was the SIXTH White Dragon!
A mess like this...
You think I'd let an illegal move like this go through!
Illegal?
But you yourself
didn't you already accept that Illegal move?
When you had two Whites in your hand,
You drew the 5th White right after declaring Riichi
Thus at that time,
You should have noticed something off with the game
Why didn't you say anything THEN?
Apparently, when it suits your purposes...
you accept what's illegal
but when it's not to your advantage you go around shouting "illegal, illegal!"
Why, that kind of play is simply not acceptable
Is it?
Don't you think so, Akagi?
Certainly, it's as you say
A-Akagi
But Harada,
Despite that, I'm quite sure...
you haven't won
What?
If you accept there are 6 White Dragon tiles
Naturally this game is an exception
And if you accept that exception
You'll have to accept my exception from the rules as well!
Ron
Head Bump
Head bump he says?
HA HA HA HA
ARE YOU FUKKIN RETARDED?
The kid discarded a WHITE DRAGON
You're waiting on a 2/5 Sou (bamboo) or a 5 Pin (dots)
Yes, on the surface
HUNH?
If there's 6 White Dragons...
That means there were tiles left out of the game
Probably three tiles of two types
I say that White that Hiroyuki discarded isn't a White at all
I say it was destined to be a missing tile I could declare Ron on
Missing tile?
Yes
That tile is precisely
a 5 Sou (5 bamboo)
If you examine the left over tiles in that Mahjong case
we'll soon know if it's among the few left over tiles
And if there's a 5 Sou among them...
you'll accept my head bump
And as it's merely a Tanyao hand
the game will simply continue
But if there isn't a 5 Sou in that case...
You're out of bounds
and the point penalty KNOCKS YOU THE FUCK OUT!
If you agree to that...
I'll accept the bet
No problem
Akagi
Please. Don't do it
The tiles the West team swapped
Only two types of tiles out of 34 in Mahjong
Choosing just the 5 sou is not a gamble you're likely to win!
I'm the one that dealt into Harada's hand...
Hiro,
It's gone too far already
Hunh?
I declared a Ron
There's no turning back
Whether or not your White should have been a 5 Sou...
Is the question at hand
BUT
Hiroyuki,
Akagi Shigeru himself has said as much
There's no taking it back
We can only watch now
Preview
Akagi has survived!
What I'm afraid of is becoming what I'm not
Don't avert your eyes from anything real
The way forward opens!