Ten wants to end it in one go
Riichi
This is the last hand!
By whatever means necessary
WE MUST WIN
Cheating fucks
I will make you regret that Riichi
Ten is aiming for both a SanSyoku and Chanta at the same time
and he's got to get a 1 Sou to get it
But
with that tile switch just now, Harada's probably followed him into Tenpai
We're in a tough spot
A Chanta SanSyoku
Going for them both at once!
I'm in Tenpai with a 3 sided wait
It's only a matter of time before I draw my winning tile!
Ten's wait is without doubt for a  1 or 4 Sou
And if he gets a 1 Sou it's Chanta and SanSyoku
But even with just the 4 Sou
If he carries additional Dora it's a Dealer win
It's a Tsumo
A Chanta SanSyoku!
They're all cleared!
Ten, You've won!
Just hold on now
We don't know just yet
Just what is he on about now?
Hiroyuki
I have not yet...
flipped the Ura-Dora
Right now
I've got a Menpin Tsumo Chanta SanSyoku
as well as an Ipeikou and 2 Dora
that's 10 Han
The upper limit of a Baiman win
In this hand...
If I should carry even ONE Ura-Dora, it's a SanBaiMan win
with only 11,300 points...
It knocks you out
HA HA HA HA
BOTTOM TEXT
How about that
Didn't you notice?
Your remarkable luck struck once too often
and it brought poison with it
DIDN'T IT?
You may have cleared the Yaku
but at the same time cleaned out a teammate
It's possible to complete both the conditions of victory and defeat simultaneously
And now everything
Is decided by the Ura-Dora
Ten!
Reveal it!
If we don't carry the Ura-Dora our team wins
Please!
Don't get it!
*TL NOTE: Ten carries two Ura-dora, making the hand valuable enough to knock Hiroyuki out.
This is not according to keikaku
Ten
Just tell me one thing
Why, in such a dangerous match...
Your hand...
It would have been better to NOT have declared Riichi
I barred the door behind me
cut off my own retreat
If I had not declared Riichi, in all probability...
it would have meant your victory
More than just ruthless playing...
without the will to snatch it, there is no victory
Mahjong where you just wait for your opponent to make a mistake offers no path
Harada,
I think you understand that just as well as I
This contest was past the point...
where it could be won by simple logic
If I had demurely avoided that Riichi
my delicate equilibrium with you would have collapsed
and I would have lost that which I needed to win
I knew it in my gut
and followed my hunch
Simply...
that's all it was
I-is this a tie?!?
MOTHER FUCKER
I did not think it would take this exceptional level of effort or time to arrive at this point
Let's settle this once and for all
Ten...
Let's settle this between us two alone
I want to beat you personally
With no one else involved!
*1V1 me
*Futari Mahjong(ふたり麻雀）: Mahjong variant with only two players. "Two Player Mahjong"
Agreed
Arrange it
You know...
I kinda think I know how Harada feels
In all probability
he's chasing a moment
A moment--?
Yeah
I feel something similar...
having carried this burden for a few years, I understand
He wants to get to the top
Just once in your life is enough
to reach that pinnacle
And in the moment when you've got it
you soon feel the hollowness of it slipping away
To people who get close to that just once...
that feeling of satisfaction is overwhelming
Harada, I dare say...
Is very sick
Honestly...
I've scarcely seen anyone more so
What else has he to live for?
Just that single moment. One way or another
He wants to feel that high again
Harada and I...
we just might be becoming more alike
#/tv/shows subs presents
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takeshi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 11
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice Guy on Tenho Way)
First an explanation of the Two Player Mahjong rules
One time...
I played it with a Kyushu boss
it's Mahjong that's a little different
This video will explain the rules
Yo
Yessir
Two Player Mahjong Baisc Rules
100,000 points is placed on another table
West Team
East Team
Dora:
Tsumo!
Tsumo:
No points are traded between players
Riizumo, White Dragon, 1 Dora: Mangan
Winning points are merely taken
East Team 8000 points Awarded
When the match is over
This winner simply has the most points collected
This style of two player Mahjong
Has a first part called Stage A
First Half: Stage A
Second Half: Stage B
2 Person Mahjong Basic Rules
And a second part called Stage B which follows
First, stage A
First Half: Stage A
This is like 4 person Mahjong with only 2 players
Two people play in the same way as 4 person Mahjong
Chii
You ca declare Chii off the player opposite
You can declare Chii off the other player
It differs as follows
West Team
East Team
Whether your hand is open or closed...
You must openly declare you are in Tenpai
if you're in Tenpai you must openly declare it
Tenpai
If your hand is closed you may also declare Riichi
Riichi
West Team
East Team
Thus ends stage A
Stage A
In this style of Mahjong
Complete
When either declares Tenpai, that style of play ends
at the point when either player declares Tenpai
The method of play previously followed completely ends
consequently speed is of the greatest advantage
West Team
East Team
The 2nd part is Stage B
2nd Half: Stage B
The side who hasn't declared Tenpai
Guesses opponents winning tile, presents 2 designated tiles
Guesses his opponent's winning tiles
Two designated tiles are presented
West Team
East Team
Desginated Tiles
Winning Tiles
if there's a winning tile among the two
the hand ends in a draw
Draw
the side attempting to win...
must without exceptions show their hand
this is to protect against false Tenpai declarations
West Team
East Team
Desginated Tiles
Winning Tiles
If there aren't any winning tiles among the two
If among the designated tiles there are no winning tiles
the side declaring tenpai has the right to 5 draws
Gets the right to make 5 draws
Tsumo!
If they haven't completed their hands in 5 draws
West Team
East Team
Desginated Tiles
Winning Tiles
Draws
5 failed draws
the stage goes back to the start
Two tiles are selected to complete the Riichi
A successful reading of the hand ends the hand
West Team
East Team
Desginated Tiles
Winning Tiles
and if they can't, the side in Tepai can draw 5 more tiles
And it repeats in this manner
this continues while there are still safe tiles remaining
Special Rule
There is a single special rule
High Score case:
Low Score case:
Riichi, Tsumo, Sansyoku
Riichi, Tsumo
If, for example, you make SanSyoku with 2 Man
the hand has wildly different valuations depending on winning tile
If you draw the lower scoring tile
you can lay the tile upside down
You can refuse the Tsumo
Tsumo!
2 Person Mahjong Basic Rules
fin
Other rules follow in that manner
Of course
It's a style of play addressing luck,
and thus
their respective power levels...
this game is an instrument to judge them
And the dealer?
It's determined at the start by die roll
And then in the next hand...
and even the hand after that...
the person who last won
will continue being dealer
That is to say
if you can't get a win
The dealership is not transferred
After that
Riichi while in Furiten is not allowed
That's just silly
And declaring Kan?
The same as in normal Mahjong
be it in either Stage A or B
it's okay as long as it doesn't change your wait
I understand
Well...
In closing there's a very important thing to remember
This contest is limited to 2 hours!
When two hours have passed the round we're in is the last one
First off this clock...
is set to ring after 100 minutes
That is,
the last bell will ring 20 minutes before the end of the match
At that time
even if you stop the bell by pressing the top of the clock
this clock will ring again after 10 minutes
So therefore...
20 minutes before the end of the match...
10 minutes before, and then...
the final bell
Those three times
All you have to judge the passage of time
are those three bells
Fine
Then let us begin
First Game
Dealer--> Ten: 0
Harada: 0
He's got it
One tile from Chanta Tenpai
If he discards the 4 or 6 Man
He can Tenpai
Tenpai!
f-fast!
Riichi
From now on we enter Stage B
Harada, right off, in order to become dealer
there's a high probability he put his hand together with speed as apriority
consequently, I suspect he's on a double sided wait beside the tile he used to declare Riichi
Damn
Tsumo!
Riizumo (Riichi + Tsumo) with one Dora
4,000 points
If he had kept the 7 Sou and discarded the 1 Sou
He'd have had a 3 way wait for a Mentanpin (Riichi + Tanyao + Pinfu) with one Dora
Why did he take a middle wait?
2nd Game
Ten: 0
Dealer--> Harada: 4000
Tenpai
He's got it
And so quickly!
Riichi
But why a middle wait on a 7 Man?
If he discarded the 8 Man he would have had a 4/7 Man double sided wait
and it would be Pinfu as well
Hunh?
Tsumo
Rizumo, Tanyao is 4,000 points
I see
Bad waits have the advantage in this Two Player Mahjong
Two sided or multi sided waits...
are stopped dead by any one of their winning tiles
They're consequently easy to read
Single tile or middle waits, however...
you've got to complete them with only single tile...
They're difficult to read
3rd Game
Dealer--> Ten: 4000
Harada: 4000
There it is!
If he completes this huge hand
The points situation will dramatically change
It might even, perhaps...
close the book on this long struggle
Pon
Whatever he gets, a 1, 4, or 7 Man, he's then got a Green or Red Dragon wait
But even if that's the case, Harada could turn it around with one step
That's the absolute best that could happen!
If he discards that 3 Pin
He's in Tenpai with a 1/7 Main wait
W-why didn't he declare Tenpai?
My god
IS HE GOING FOR A DAISANGEN?
Harada will soon be in Tenpai
You can't do this. Ten!
There isn't time for a hand above this
Damn. He's in Furiten?
Amazing
What a fucking draw!
That Green Dragon is the last one including the Dora indicator
To draw it now!
And because he drew it now...
Next turn he'll draw single tile wait that can't be read
Will he declare Riichi?
Don't do it!
We did it
No Riichi!
Kan
WTF
Ohhhh...
Harada doesn't think Ten has a hidden Green Dragon triplet
Letting Harada know he's going for a DaiSanGen...
Harada will choose a Green Dragon to complete it
that will be his priority
Ten's single tile wait is the worst possible
Harada has already discarded one of them
so there's only one remaining
but he can't wait any more
If he gives Harada just one more chance...
he'll for sure declare Riichi
There's no choice but to take the 5 Man single wait
T-TEN?!?
You're STILL waiting?
If Harada declares Riichi
all this will come to nothing!
It's his turn again!
Harada,
I've kept you waiting
I declare Tenpai
That's crazy!
Why Man tiles?
How did he know it was Man tiles?
From Ten's discards...
it's difficult to imagine it could be Man tiles
Looks more like a by-the-book Sou Honisou that doesn't need Man tiles