Tenho Way
Riichi Mahjong Minami
2nd floor
Ron
8 Thousand points
Again!?
He's defeated all the regulars
Are you a pro, breh?
No
While I was learning probability at university
I wondered what would happen if it were applied to Mahjong
I wanted to try an experiment
Experiment?
There are a total of 136 tiles in Mahjong
There's a 3% chance of drawing the tile you want
With such a low probability, what will happen?
that's the theory anyhow
Well, I've had enough
Anyone want to join in next?
Get Ten
ShinMiyaTei Restaurant
Hey. Yakisoba up
Ten, here's your Soseki Soba.
Sorry for the wait
Ten! You've got to come with me!
Can't you see what I'm doing?
Right now...
I'm eating yakisoba
You're eating yakisoba NOW?
Have you ever eaten it yourself?
In my entire life
the yakisoba at this place
is the best on the planet
Okay. Okay. After you eat...
Come play! He's a young guy but...
he's really strong and took the all regulars to the cleaners!
What kind of guy is it?
He's as precise as a computer, with no weaknesses!
Pops. Thanks for the grub
Thank you Ten
Ron
5,100 points
Shit
Looks like I've got to quit
Oh, you're sure winning ain't you
Will you play ME?
#/tv/shows bible study and thermos discussion goup
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takeshi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice Guy on Tenho Way)
Episode 1
So, a wager between you and I?
I'm confident anything will be fine .Only...
Let's do a side bet
Side bet?
If I win, you give back what you won from everyone
I don't need any money
And if you lose?
I double your winnings
You're a ringer, aren't you?
Yeah. Something like that.
I've been wanting to meet someone like you
As I haven't yet beenbeaten in Mahjong,
I thought I could become a ringer myself
Well then it's decided
At the table over there?
A non-automatic table must be so he can cheat
That's got to be it
If he didn't do that he couldn't be sure to beat someone he doesn't know
Hand stacking tiles isn't a problem is it?
No
No problem
East Round 1
The contest is one East South round, and whoever has more points wins, even if its merely 100 more
First I have to make sure there's no cheating
I can't do a single wait on an undiscarded tile, but...
I'll apply some pressure
Riichi
Ron
12,000 points
South Round 1
Ron
8,000 points.
What's with this character? The silent type
South Round 2
Pon
Ron
12,000 points.
Even a novice wouldn't deal into that
All that remains is this guy's turn as dealer
But I'm in the lead by 50,000 points
Just what is he playing at?
Hell happened? A blackout?
Turn on the lights!
S-sorry. I hit the switch with my elbow
Ten. It's your turn
Ah. I got this
*Tenhou Chuuren PouTou
*Chuuren PouTou(九連宝燈) Special Yakuman (high scoring hand) "The Nine gates"
* Tenhou (天和): Dealer completes hand on first tile draw
He did it!
Typical Ten. It's a complete reversal of 90,000 points!
This is not possible! You cheated!
Will you admit it?
I see
Mahjong
is a truly fearsome thing isn't it?
Just hold on a second.
Admit you cheated
Cheat?
When you arranged your hand the tile wall in front of you moved a tiny amount
Somehow or other it was a brilliant trick of the tiles
Aren't you, a pro, embarrassed to do something so childish?
A sneaky underworld guy like you
I could become a ringer right now
Oh
Don't make me laugh
And what's your name?
Name
Igawa Hiroyuki
Hiroyuki, hunh?
Well, then
Being a ringer...
is the business of shouldering the burden of other people's lives
People bet more than their lives
Whether by guile or cheating outright
you have to win by any means necessary
Are you happy to win such a low victory?
How can you be content playing the Mahjong of a charlatan?
That
is being a Pro
It's regrettable but,
the sweet world you imagine is very far from the truth
I got no use for you
I watched your Mahjong very closely
In that match, Ten did cheat.
You won.
Your ability...
Won't you test it once more?
Excuse me
Oh Sawada! Come in, come in
This is our ringer for the game
Ringer?
Boy, he's a young one
He's got the chops
Ah. What's this about?
I'm in real estate
Call me Maruo
I'm Igawa
Really, this is about a deed
and you'll play Mahjong for it
a deed for a... plot of land?
Yeah. I'm looking to get his fortune.
I already own half of his home and property by gambling and debt
And the remaining half,
will be dealt with by Mahjong
Sawada found you for your strength in Mahjong
Sorry
Yes?
Hello, this is Maruo
These guys are pure trash, but they're the most powerful gang right now
We've got to take shelter where we can
Even if it means protecting garbage like that
But in such an important deal can I...
Stop right there. I KNOW
I've seen a lot of ringers before now
You're hiding an ability far beyond that crowd
Have confidence in your own Mahjong
I'm betting on you
You can do it, can't you?
Being a ringer,
Is the business of shouldering the burden of other people's lives
I got no use for you
Yes.
Please, Igawa-chan.
After you take his shop, how about a victory celebration?
Keep your mind on the game
Yes
Sorry I'm late
Nakanishi!
Did you bring the deed like a good boy?
It's here
And your friend?
Ten!
Perfect
I've wanted to see a contest against you one more time
And this time I won't lose
Whatever your cheats
The contest is 5 East South rounds.
The winner is the first to take 3 rounds.
One thing
Me and Hiroyuki...
make the game the difference between our points.
What will you do?
Nothing. It's no problem
Well, then. It's decided
Ten. Just what are you plotting?
First Game
East Round One
In this situation, Ten can't possibly cheat
I ought to be vigilant against anything he does
But this Nakanishi guy...
Chii
A Man (character tile) single suit hand, hunh?
Oh, you've already got enough of them
I'm not in Tenpai
And I'm not in Tenpai
First Game
East Round 3
This time he's collecting Pin (dot) tiles
Discarding the Dora tile after he drew it?
He couldn't make such dangerous discards from a worthless hand so often
As I thought. He's about to win
Damn
I can't discard Pin tiles
And I can't discard from this meld near the Dora
It can't be helped
Ron
7,700 points
What a shit break
First Game
South Round 4
Pon.
Riichi
He discarded the Dora within one turn of Sawada's Riichi
Ordinarily no one would consider discarding that
Nakanishi's certainly got a single suit hand
Ron
2,000 points
If you play so sluggishly, you'll lose
He's confusing you
What you don't know is scaring you
Please help me!
Ten!
I need a ringer because my dead mom left this place to me
PLEASE!
I'll do it since I owe you
You've led an honest, straightforward life...
How could you gamble it all away?
Basically I was tricked
I was cheated out of everything in a light game of poker
Before I noticed they had half my shop!
Of course
All things considered, you just can't beat them
PLEASE!
Please save me!
Ten. I'm pleading with you!
Pops
Can you become a heretic?
A... heretic?
Up to now you've led an honest, straightforward life
But that's no good for this contest
This shop, your land...
If you don't want them to be stolen
become a heretical, UNORTHODOX player for me
Ten knows Nakanishi has been faking single suit hands
it's all been a bluff
Only,
They've put his shop on the line
Nakanishi...
It's a bluff burned into his soul.
And when you carry something like that this far
It's not a matter of catching people in tricks or anything like that.
I'd call it more "divine"
A direct attack.
you might call it "madness"
They're willing to lose it all
I don't know what we do next
Well then. Round two
Shall we begin?
People can obtain what they desire through HOPE
Preview
BUT IN GAMBLING IT'S JUST THE OPPOSITE
It can't end for me like this
What on earth is he doing?
How did he read my discards?
That's the Mahjong level I'm at