"Clear" Mahjong?
Designated yaku
The team that clears them first, wins
If that's your gut feeling
It's okay.
I'll take it
Ron.
SanAnKou cleared
#/tv/shows subs presents
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takeshi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 10
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice Guy on Tenho Way)
West Team:
Harada: 25000 Soga: 25000
East Team:
Ten: 49000 Hiroyuki: 1000
I missed a pair?
Could I get a chitoitsu like this?
The alternative is a called Tanyao
Chii
Pon
Shit!
My chance gone in one moment
Soga's without doubt in Tenpai
According to his discards...
his wait is most probably
a 3, 6 Pin wait
I'm in Tenpai
But, it's one step too late
If I had reached Tenpai just one turn earlier
Ten could have dealt me a 6 Pin
but in the current situation
a 6 Pin is Soga's winning tile
He'd Head Bump
Ten can't possibly deal it to me
やつは今
Even now the little guy
しくじりながらも懸命になんとかしようとしている
despite his failure, he's trying his utmost
その意気に賭けよう
I'll bet on his determination
There's most probably still one 6 Pin left in the wall
He got it
With that last draw the Kid's hand is ready
Supposing his Chitoitsu fell apart...
he's waiting on this very 6 Pin or a 9 Pin
only now he's aiming for a Tanyao
And at this moment he can't possibly draw a 6 Pin!
according to his discards, Ten is certainly holding a 6 Pin
But he's read Soga's wait
and he can't deal into it
and I just drew the 4th 6 Pin!
The kid's Tanyao is nipped in the bud
The only remaining ways he could win
are winning off the last draw or the last discard
I'll erase those hopes as well!
Chii
* Take that
* By his two Chii calls, Harada has changed the draw order so the final draw no longer goes to Hiroyuki
I've cheated you of a final draw win
now your win is bugger all
It's over
there's two more turns
but this hand is already done
If I discard the 9 Pin I'm in Tenpai
9 Pin is one of the kid's winning tiles
but outside calling it on the final discard
the moron's got no Yaku
therefore If I get into Tenpai
In this hand, the kid...
will end up with a no Tenpai penalty
a 1,500 or 1,000 point penalty
it's over if that happens in his current state
And the kid can't deal into a hand either
And if it comes down to it...
I'll blow him away with a Tsumo
If even that happens losing merely 500 points is huge
Pon
He's still holding onto those?
The last draw which I took pains to shift to Soga
Is with that kid again!
There's no more 6 Pin tiles to draw
He's aming to draw the final 9 Pin, isn't he
Kan
A Rinshan replacement draw?
At any rate
it's all the same if he's betting on a single draw
That possibility is paper thin
It's only natural he didn't draw it
the natural result
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
実ったぞ
The fruit has ripened
はい
I understand
Ripened?
What's he on about?
Kan
OH FUCK
Yes...
Dealing into a hand doesn't have to come from the discards
Ron
ChanKan, 3 Dora
8,000 points
the FUCK did I do...?
Pon
Ten's 9 Pin Pon call
It wasn't a Pon call when he had two tiles
It was a Pon call when he had THREE
Then the Kid, from Ten's hand
took the remaining 9 Pin!
West Team:
Harada: 25000 Soga: 25000
East Team:
Ten: 41000 Hiroyuki: 9000
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
生き延びたな
You survived
Yes, I did
Now Hiroyuki has a safety buffer
And thus the biggest difference...
The East team, having gotten a SanAnKou
gives them an overwhelming advantage
FUCK SHIT PISS
West Team:
Harada: 25000 Soga: 25000
East Team:
Ten: 41000 Hiroyuki: 9000
East Hand 3
Chii
Ron!
That's Ittsu
Tsumo
Chitoitsu
Runnn
Ron
Ittsu
TSUMO!
Chanta!!!
The game's going back and forth
but as I thought
Ten's initial win
that SanAnKou has done its work
West Team:
Harada: 4400 Soga: 38600
East Team:
Ten: 39700 Hiroyuki: 17300
2nd Game
South Hand 3
If they clear a Chanta and Sansyoku
then...
it's ZA ENDO
The time that remains...
there's only a little left
5 or 6 hands
No...
less than 2 or 3
A SanAnKou...
If I complete a similar SanAnKou...!
Got it!
Chii
Pon
Ten's fast too
If he can discard a 7 Sou he'll clear SanSyoku
In this situation he's simply got to discard the 7 Sou
He's somehow in Tenpai, isn't he
There's a good chance his wait is above 6 Pin
Is it Chanta hand?
He's got it!!!
If he discards the 8 Pin he's in Tenpai for a SanAnKou
but it's likely that's the tile the other side is waiting for
I clearly can't win waiting for an 8 Pin
If I complete this hand...
with merely a double South Wind it's only 3,200 points
and there ain't many turns left
Kan
you CLOWN
舐めた真似しよって
He's making like he's given up!
Calling Kan on 9 Pin and discarding his 8 Pin
all while passing on the 8 Pin I discarded
This little act of yours
I'll make you regret it!
He hasn't completed his SanAnKou yet
but a Pinhu, Ipeikou, 2 Dora hand is Mangan
Take the hand!
According to his discards Harada's aiming for SanAnKou
and Ten a Chanta
they're both simply ignoring faster winning hands!
the idea of "clearing" hands is of more advantage
oh shiiii
Only one left
And with this...
RON
3,000 (non-dealer)/ 6,000 (dealer) points
AND SANANKOU CLEARED
やられた
We're done for
万全を尽くした天さんが敗れ、
Ten thought he covered all possibilities, but still lost
一鉄を通した原田が勝った
and Harada's Ironclad persistence paid off
すでにこの場は通常の定石確率は通用しない
by-the-book probabilities are already useless in a game like this
West Team:
Harada: 16400 Soga: 35600
East Team:
Ten: 36700 Hiroyuki: 11300
2nd Game
Final Hand
An absolutely terrible starting hand
Chii
A SanSyoku?
h-he's fast!
He's ready
In Tenpai for a Sansyoku with 1 Dora
but Harada is most likely in Tenpai as well
間に合うのか
Is he in time?
So he's in Tenpai...
まずい、差し込まれたか
This is bad. Soga's dealt into Harada's hand
まだ原田は聴牌していない
Harada must not be in Tenpai yet
天さんの待ちは恐らく索子の下辺り、
Ten's wait is most likey on lower Sou tiles
天さんがツモるか
If Ten can draw his winning tile...
俺が差し込めれば
or If I deal into his hand
この局は勝てる
we can win this hand!
Got it!
Why?!?
原田の手の速さを見たら
Considering Harada's speed
欲張らず三色だけでも和了っておくべき
He ought not be greedy and just take the SanSyoku win here
Of course,
He wants a Chanta AND SanSyoku
Ten aims to end this all in one go
He can call on THIS tile
W-wait
Why did Soga discard that 5 Sou
If Harada had called that 5 Sou
we all know it should have completed his SanSyoku
but Harada didn't call it!
The 5 Sou is a clue regarding Harada's SanSyoku
Soga wouldn't purposefully discard it for nothing
There's something there...
そうか
I see!
原田の三色、
Harada's SanSyoku
そもそもあれが目くらまし
It was all a smokescreen after all
Soga's discards...
at first glance they look like dscards for normal TanYao Pinfu hand
But if you also consider the 5 Man and 6 Pin Harada called...
AND the tiles I called
they're the textbook discards of a Honiisou
Probably a double South Wind Honisou 1 Dora Haneman
With only 11,300 points, I'll be knocked out
やつらは
That is to say, these bastards...
鼻から三色など眼中にない
they've been disregarding a SanSyoku from the start
点棒で俺を脱落させるつもりだったんだ
Their intention is to knock me out by points
こいつら
These fucks
なんて事考えやがる
To think something like that up
ちっ、気付いたか
Tsk. He's noticed hasn't he
きりそうな気配だったのに
Even though all the signs were erased
Soga's colorless, odorless...
closed Honiisou wait
よくぞ気付いた。ひろゆき
Good eye, Hiroyuki
He got it
A 1 Sou wait Tenpai
If he draws a 1 Sou it's a Chanta SanSyoku
A 4 Sou will also most probably come out in time
But whether he should Riichi or not...
those around would become extra vigilant
the best move is just to stay silent
Riichi
こいつら、
Cheating fucks
またせこい手を使いやがって
Yet another underhanded move
Now I'm in Tenpai with a 3 sided wait
今は最終局面、
This is the final hand!
どんな手を使っても
By whatever means necessary
勝たなきゃいかんのや
WE MUST WIN
そのリーチ、
and that Riichi you just declared
後悔させたるわ
I'll make you regret it
This is quickly looking like a contest we can't win
Just wait a moment, now
I'm going to take you down!
TWO PLAYER MAHJONG