Osaka
Two years later
Mahjong New Maruko
All automatic tables
It's been two years
I left Tokyo,
Just wandering
I found a life,
but after being here for six months
I instead felt a longing to play Mahjong
Not Mahjong among friends
REAL Mahjong
Ron
8,000 points
That's his fifth straight win
he's just too good
Has he lost？
He's truly skillful
the sort that makes you hesitant to breathe, anxious
that makes you sit on pins and needles
THAT Mahjong
Pretty impressive, kiddo
I like what I see
I'm lookin for a player like you
Care for a dink?
An East/West contest?
The top ringers from *Kanto and *Kansai get together
* Kantō is around Tokyo in the east of Japan
*Kansai is around Osaka in the (so called) West
and then
it's an underworld Mahjong East/West battle
And you want me to join the West team?
No, no, no
I ain't West
Why is someone from the East team HERE?
This goes down here in Osaka TOMORROW, hell or high water!
One of our players didn't come in from Tokyo
So we're looking for someone strong
I'm looking for players real quick, so I'm meeting with you
My breh...
he's the boss of the East team
My bro's on a different level
He's strong enough to win countless games
Well, then. The East should win easy
It ain't that simple
The West has a monster of their own
Monster?
While being the Boss of the Kansai Yakuza
he's also a ringer
Harada Katsumi
With his overwhelming money, power and connections
He's scouting for players of ability
What happens if you win?
A monopoly on the skim
Wha?
If you win...
Countrywide, each and every Mahjong parlor contributes a 10,000 Yen payment per day
That daily 10,000 yen payment amounts to 100 Million yen per day
for a full year
You get *36.5 billion yen
* More than 300 Million USD in 2019
Amazing
A tale to set your heart dancing!
So how about it? Will you join the East camp?
You gotta decide right away
I'll introduce you to my brah right away
Bro is here right now playing a game with the West team
That's the guy I mentioned. The boss ringer
The West team head, Harada Katsumi
Even among ringers he's indisputably a player of the highest level
A genius that has been called the 2nd Akagi
And the head of the East team?
My breh is playing there, right in front
The man who dealt the invincible Akagi his only defeat
Who with the strength of countless wins has repeatedly made the impossible possible
The head of the East team
Ten Takashi
#/tv/shows linux ricing and online swimming lessons community presents:
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Ten Takashi
Kishitani Goro
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Igawa Hiroyuki
Furukawa Yuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety...
息を殺して
you hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street,
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 5
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice Guy on Tenho Way)
What round it it?
South Hand 4, last round
The guy from Tokyo is in 3rd
3rd place?
But his last hand is good
the sort of hand that could pull off a sudden reversal if it gets big
He's got it!
Honiisou, ShoSan with one dora. A Baiman hand that can put him on top
If he's bold he can discard a 3/6/9 for a single wait on Red Dragon
Later he could draw a Red dragon for a 3rd turn as dealer
Furthermore this guy's going for Chitoitsu (all pairs hand).
A previously undiscarded tile like Red Dragon could be dangerous
Ron
6,400 points
oh, darn
so waiting on Red Dragon, hunh?
Y-you two KNOW each other?
A little
How you been?
o-okay
Ten
Today you lost on purpose, didn't you
It's clear...
There was no reason for you to discard the Red Dragon there
Of course. Leave it to you to...
I didn't want to show them my hand
my skill, yeah
but also my luck
I didn't want to show them... my game flow
So THAT'S the number one guy on the East team?
This'll be a blowout for the West team won't it
HOLD ON NOW
Turn over Ten's subsequent draws from the point he lost
y-yessir
A Red Dragon, no?
yes
but, how?
You lot couldn't possibly understand, but
that guy could SENSE there was a Red Dragon coming
You thought the Eastern head was pure trash,
it don't look like that at all
You're late
The 3rd member of the East team
Asai "Ganpai" Ginji
Ganpai: (lit. "wounded tile") is the cheat of marking tiles
A most valued artisan
through which almost no opponent can see
His skill at handling tiles is near that of an acrobat
So what happened? We still need one man for the East team?
It's no good
A notable ringer took the cash and simply vanished
burns me the fuck up
Without doubt this contest is gonna be tough to win
And Akagi?
I looked, but couldn't get him
I see
Breh
How about him?
No
He's no good for the East team
Why?
I told you to wash your hands of this world
This battle
Is no place for a normie like you
But at least he's got the game
and some spirit
Just try me
for as far as you can use me
For two long years I've been restless
I've been waiting for this moment!
and so
NO
Fight your battles in the normie world
It... suits you
Kid, how old are you?
Rash, brash...
reckless
He's got a good look bout him, doesn't he
He looks just like you did, Ten. Long ago
Our opponents won't be expecting a greenhorn like this
He might just be our... trump card
Put him in
Please
通天閣
Tsū-TEN-kaku
The West team roster
Harada Katsumi
Mitsui Jyuuji
Akutsu Tetsu
Soga Mitsui
Hunh?
What's the matter?
Soga's name is here
Those West bastards
They even pulled Soga into this?
Soga?
Who is that?
A master who controlled the underworld for years
Over a ten year period he didn't lose once
But I heard he retied because of poor health
My god. To think even Soga is here
First, there is a proposal from the West team
What is it?
What if both teams
on top of normal Mahjong rules
attach a single additional condition
as you prefer
Understood
The East team players
here you are
Ten Takashi
Asai Ginji
Isokaze Ken
Igawa Hiroyuki
The East team looks useless
Ten's the only smart one
It doesn't look like the East team could get Akagi
Even though we went to great pains to get Soga...
it's looking like it's going to be a dull match
ha ha ha
A Fukumoto Nobuyuki appears!
It will be time momentarily.
Please proceed to the contest area
Let's go
There is a time restriction rule
Anyone caught cheating hands over his point box
Among the 8 people here
only four will advance to the final round
And our proposed additional rule
Mangan-Shibari
Mangan-Shibari (満貫縛り): A rule restricting winning hands to Mangan or higher. No "trivial" wins.
Wins less than Mangan are just useless
And there is no penalty for not achieving Tenpai
Agreed
And yours?
How about a rule eliminating accumulated wins?
Hunh?
Normally points go to the winner
but now, the points of someone who wins a hand...
would absolutely never increase
This rule...
ensures an upset is always possible with a single direct hit
If points don't increase someone with no points can't recover
and if you deal into someone's hand, it instantly starts a countdown to death
HA HA HA
Sounds like fun!
We accept
East Hand 1
Riichi
F-fast
On only the 3rd turn
Even with a Mangan-shibari?
That was a risky discard
Certainly, seeing discards like that, it on the contrary makes me SUSPICIOUS of Sou (bamboo) tiles
therefore I guess other tiles are okay, but I don't know...
This Riichi is meant to measure the skill of these two
Or to put it another way,
to find which is an easy mark
Looking at the bias in his discards
anyone would have a bad feeling about Sou tiles
Ken went with his gut feeling, as he's the type that acts on hunches
But...
Hiroyuki is the type that places logic as a priority.
He'll follow theory in this situation
and he'll certainly play the appropriate safe tile, BUT
that normal style of playing is the worst here
Based on Mitsui's discards, I've got the 4th and last 2 Sou
this OUGHT to pass here
Ron
Well, one Ura-dora of two
kid...
You're lucky
but
to fall for a hackneyed trap like this
You're not worth talking about
East Hand 3
ah...
s-sorry
H-he's missing a tile!
He's only got 12!
He's in Shohai. What an incompetent mistake
Shōhai(少牌): Having too few tiles
Izzat a 1 Pin?
RON
SuuAnKou (4 concealed triplets)
He's no longer in Shohai!
H-he's done the UNTHINKABLE
Among the rules of Mahjong, that one known as Shohai is a peculiarly odd
While it's clearly a foul, you can't stop the game for it. Only disregard a win
And that's my advantage
When I'm in Shohai, no one pays me any attention
I never thought I could take down Harada with a clean game
All that's needed is for him to see I have the full 13 tiles when I reveal my hand
The wall before me has an East wind on the end
Only I saw it when I knocked it over before
so, putting the East wind and 6 Sou from the wall in my hand
I can pull the 1 Pin Harada discarded on the first turn
Take the 1 Pin and switch it out
So I can pull an East wind and 1 Pin into my hand
completing my SuuAnKou single tile wait
All that remains to to RON Harada on his 1 Pin
SuuAnKou
47,000 points
The contest is over
H-harada dealt into a dealer Yakuman!
Hey now
Don't take us for fools
That wall in front of you went from 9 tiles to 8 tiles wide
It's obvious you pulled two tiles from that wall
the hell you on about m8?
YOU FUCKER!
Mitsui
just be quiet a moment
BUT
If anyone is going to fight over this, it's me
And I'll SETTLE IT
You're called "Ken" aren't you?
I'll be sure to remember your name
Ken clearly pulled two tiles from his wall
And he's still got ONE IN HIS HAND
What's he going to do?
Cut away man
But if there's no tile in that hand
with that cut you only confirm
YOU LOSE
Do you know...
When someone dies from a gunshot wound
they die senseless, in shock
however...
death by stabbing is a LOT more painful
w-what are you saying？
This Mahjong is a scramble over life and death!
If I confirm my opponent is cheating I take his life!
and I'll do so at my leisure
AT AN AUTOPSY
S-STOP PLEASE
Too late
HA HA HA HA
This man kills without qualm
Preview
Akagi!
I thought I'd mix it up a bit
Let us confirm your two players
My short sword will taste blood
Hiroyuki is cornered
It's over