Having both Akagi and Ten completes the East team
I'm a laughing stock
It's a tough game
So be tough
Not a single flaw or mark
Ginji is out!
I'm done
Okay
There's only three of you left
One of you will play each hand to the end
And the other two
Will change places on the 10th turn
The three of you rotating
taking each position in turn
So
Agreed?
Yes
Agreed
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: disqual
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 25000
Game 6
East Hand 1
Holy shit. To think that Ginji's gone
Pon
A 7 Man dora
The dora have been flowing to Soga
Riichi
Soga in this, the 4th hand
Is aiming for a Chitoitsu
Declaring Riichi on a Dora Haitei draw
there's a possibility of a Dora pair
so it's Mangan
The fact that I've got 3 of the Dora
means there's but one in his hand
A Dora single tile wait
And since he's on a Dora wait, if he draws it himself his hand reaches Haneman
But as I've collected 3 Dora during play
Soga's wait has vanished
Just unlucky I guess
Riichi
Your wait is already dead
I see
He's accumulated 3 Dora, hasn't he
Take it, Akagi
It's a gift from me
The 4th Dora tile?
You did that, didn't you Soga
Now this is something to see
I'm deliberately provoking Akagi
And he's not the kind to back down
Let's just see if he'll try to use that Dora I gave him to win
As I thought
The kid's at the table
Akagi's hand, with an Ippatsu Tsumo,
and 4 Dora, it's a Haneman
But if he wins, he'll drop the kid's points to 1,000
Therefore...
he'll let the win pass
I drew it
Tsumo
It's about time
Chitoitsu Tsumo with 2 Ura-Dora
Haneman
You've got to win when you can
I see you calling tiles...
But winning's the thing, isn't it?
Akagi...
open your eyes
Stop screwing around and wiping other people's ass for them
You'll end up dead
East Team
Ten: 19000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 22000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 22000
Game 6
South Hand 1
Since Soga's Haneman
The game flow has been on the West side
OhhhKAY
Tsumo. Tanpin, Sansyoku, one Dora
Haneman
East Team
Ten: 16000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 16000
Game 6
South Hand 3
Tsumo
With an additional Dora
A Baiman win
Winning while one of your own is the dealer
hits him for double the points
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
It delivers damage to friend and foe alike
despite all this, Soga still took the win
Preventing us from overcoming the vast difference in points between east and west takes priority
And now Hiroyuki is...
on the edge of a cliff
#/tv/shows Talmudic Scholars and Golems present:
カンカン照り ギラついた
太陽みたいな
Blazing hot, like the blistering sun
Kishitani Goro
Ten Takashi
あいつがまた帰ってきた
He's come back again
Furukawa Yuki
Igawa Hiroyuki
ざわざわと
In anxiety
息を殺して
You hold your breath
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
誰の肩に止まるかな
Whose shoulder will it land upon
くるくる廻る天道虫
Ladybug going round and round
背中の星が揃ったら
When the stars on her back align
雨上がりの風吹く通りを
After the rain, above the windswept street
#/tv/shows subs: "They're better than nothing!"
陽が昇った
The sun rose
#/tv/shows subs are presented in classic Piss Yellow™️
Episode 7
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(The Nice guy on Tenho Way)
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 7
East Hand 2
One more tile and I'm in Tenpai
Got it
But If I declare Riichi, I don't think the 6 or 9 Man will come out
*DAMATEN
*Damaten: Forgo declaring riichi, keeping your Tenpai status secret
Akagi ought to have already noted my Chanta hand
but despite whatever he's noticed, he still might discard a Green Dragon
giving me a huge win
Riichi
Declaring Riichi with an extremely dangerous Dora
He's got a Sansyoku
or Chiniitsou
FUCK
With that 6 Man I don't reach Mangan
But right now
I've got no choice but to take it
Ron
South, Red Dragon, one Dora
6,400 points
We survived
Harada flinched under Akagi's pressure
Akagi's odd discards overcame his spirit
Akagi declared Riichi when he wasn't ready to go out
It was a bluff
For good or ill,
If the witness came by or if the match came to a draw, his fake riichi would be found out
that would mean an 8,000 point penalty
A NO TENPAI SUICIDE RIICHI
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 7
South Hand 1
Chii
Pon
A Sou (bamboo) only hand?
They fucking did it
I've got tenpai
That is, if I discard 7 Man i'm in Tenpai
but as they swapped tiles I can't discard it
Soga was passed something like a Dora hidden triplet
Aiming to win with a Tanyao with 3 Dora
so Tanyao tiles he hasn't discarded won't pass
I absolutely can't deal into his hand
They're playing damn dirty Mahjong
Pon
W-why?
After that tile switch, what Harada's waiting on is tough to pin down
Rather than Pon that 9 Sou safe tile, wouldn't it be better to hold onto it?
Holy shit
He didn't notice the swap?
He didn't see Harada swap the tiles when changing seats!
Ron
Tanyao with 3 dora
Mangan
How you figure that?
Hunh?
How have you got 3 Dora?
HE SWAPPED THE DORA
YOU FUUUUUUUU----
Hell, swapping the dora indicator like that
To imagine that in a mere instant...
That wasn't a conscious decision
My hands were moving on their own
In the midst of a game I seldom use my head
just my guts
Follow them above all else
Follow your gut instinct?
The only opportunity you have to follow chance is in THE NOW
The feelings in your gut summon opportunity
Cultivate them, raise them up
The result:
you'll open the door to victory
And THIS opportunity
It WON'T escape us
From here on out
The East team's counterattack begins!
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 8
East Hand 3
I've got a great hand
SanAnKou, Green Dragon and one Dora
Even without declaring Riichi it's certainly a Mangan hand
He drew a 4 Man
He'll declare a closed Kan, I guess
H-he DIDN'T KAN!?!?!
W-why?
Riichi
It can't be!
A 2-5 wait?
that valuable SanAnKou just vanished!
He's got a Riichi, Green Dragon, 1 Dora hand
6,400 points at most
WHY?
I see what's going on
Harada's playing defensively
playing consecutive safe tiles
The West team won't deal into his hand!
He's got an impossible winning tile
He can't possibly draw a 2/5 Man
Kan
Kan?
But Akagi's wait is most probably low Man tiles
There's no reason why he should discard that tile!
I've got a safe North Wind tile, but...
I've got a dora and kan-dora in my hand
If I draw the North Wind I've got a Haneman hand
It shouldn't be any problem...
if I discard a lower Sou tile
What?
Too bad
but that's it
No Ura-dora
It's only a Mangan hand
He changed his wait AFTER declaring riichi
So he couldn't declare Kan
Then, using an ILLEGAL Kan
He scalped Harada!
It was difficult to notice from the West team's perspective
while the tile he actually drew was hidden in his palm
he returned the tile he could actually Kan with to his hand
So there was unmistakably 4 tiles to Kan in his hand
With movements so fluid
It looked like there was nothing amiss
And with this *illegal Kan
*Illegal Kan: Players may only Kan when drawing the tile that completes their set of 4. Here Akagi used slight of hand to Kan when he drew an unrelated tile. This also breaks the separate rule which does not allow changing waits after delaring Riichi. lmfao
from a 2-5 Man wait...
he instantly went to a 1 Sou single tile wait
Because of there were already two 2 Sou tiles in the discards...
Harada couldn't dodge this 1 Sou wait
CAMOUFLAGE is what you do before you delcare Riichi
It's a Mahjong PREREQUISITE
Akagi turned that requirement itself on its head
an upset itself in disguise
A 1 Sou single tile wait!
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada: 7000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 8
South Hand 1
Ron
Jyunchan, SanSyoku
With dealer bonus it's 12,000 points
Akagi's declared Riichi when not in tenpai...
and that Illegal Kan has begun to tilt the game flow to the East team
East Team
Ten: 12000 Hiroyuki: 3000
Akagi: 16000
West Team
Harada:7000 Mitsui: 5000
Soga: 25000 Akutsu: 11000
Game 9
East Hand 3
Pon
He's getting cocky
Going for a toitoi or honiisou hand
by putting together East and West triplets
he's got a Mangan hand
I'm in Tenpai
But if this Chitoitsu hand doesn't carry any Dora
it won't even amount to a Mangan
Kan
Whatever contest I enter...
I ain't afraid what some pipsqueak with only 3000 points left plays
Whatever happens
he's going down
I've got this Hand
Pon
A Tanyao or Sansyoku?
Moreover with the remaining 5 pin Dora
He carries Three Dora
If he's gathered up a Toitoi it's a baiman hand
Okaay. With this tile I've got a Tanyao
A Mangan without even declaring Riichi
This hand is just between me and Akagi
Pon
The brat's also in Tenpai
He's going for a single suit hand?
Interesting
He wants to die that badly
well, I'll knock him out of the game
Harada looks like he's holding a Pinzu (dots) Honisou hand
and they expect him to discard a 5 pin?
Well THAT'S a style of play I've never thought of before
Pon
If I discard the 3 Sou I'll take the hand...
but that previous 5 Pin discard
Considering the kid's Honiisou the 3 Sou is extremely dangerous
Harada could be in Tenpai
I'll choose to deal into his hand
I'll discard a 2 Pin
At this point I've got to do what I've got to do
Ron
Head Bump
Head Bump or Atamahane(頭跳ね): In the case of two Ron calls, awarding the Ron to the player closest to the discarder, in wind order. This is in contrast to the Double Ron (or Triple Ron) rule which allows multiple point payouts on simultaneous Ron calls.
East West Toitoi 3 Dora
A Haneman win
Even though Hiroyuki had 4 Dora he avoided declaring Kan
Aiming instead to win via a much more effective single tile wait
Thus Hiroyuki chose a 2 Pin wait
As Hiroyuki  SEEMED to have a sou Honiisou, it wasn't a likely wait
Then, discarding one of his Dora...
a direct hit here would mean instant death
But...
what if it passed?
it becomes the ULTIMATE camouflage
The kid's been cautious up to now
How can he now play putting his life on the line?
Maybe the answer...
is in Akagi's hand
That hand there
is a bluff
Akagi wasn't aiming for a win himself
but rather to protect the kid
He shielded him
and that's emboldened the kid
It's been transmitted
The ultimate sensibility of an Akagi Shigeru
His spirit
This ain't good
Hiroyuki
HE'S TRANSFORMED
YOU DICK!
Preview
I've already decided what we have to do
This is battle of base instinct
Abandon yourself entirely to it
I WON'T ACCEPT THIS KIND OF MAHJONG!