An East/West Competition?
There is a time limit rule
And Mangan Shibari
The winner's points never increase
H-he's not in Shohai any longer.
He's done the UNTHINKABLE
If I confirm my opponent is cheating I TAKE HIS LIFE
PLEASE STOP!
I CAN SEE EVERYTHING YOU'RE THINKING
This round
The edge tile Ken took WAS in his right hand
Ken made a fist to convince Harada his surplus tile was still in his right hand
stab away mane
while really he was holding the extra tile in his LEFT hand
But Harada wouldn't let that cheat pass
This man
he kills without qualm
Ken!
it's okay
H-holding that tile saved me
Hey!
Nisokaze Ken :Disqualified
And one is eliminated
Who the hell are you?!
You can't go in there!
#/tv/shows subs presents
Goro Takeshi
Ten Takeshi
Furukawa Yuki
Igawa Hiroyuki
Yoshida Eisaku
Akagi Shigeru
Ten: Tenho-doori no Kaidanji
(Nice guy on the path of Tenho)
Episode 6
You rightly removed someone.
Could I mix it up a bit?
Hunh?!
He was disqualified for cheating!
We didn't agree on any replacements!
Yeah
You've come too late
Let's just wait a moment now
Having both Akagi and Ten completes the East team
We can smash them BOTH in one go
can't we, Soga?
Only...
If you'll allow us a new rule
I'll approve the substitution
Is that much agreed?
Yes
10th turn alternate playing
Wha?
On the 10th discard you stop playing and switch with your teammate behind you
You might call it...
pair cooperative playing
A MAHJONG TAG TEAM MATCH
Playing in this way
at this single table 8 men can play one hand
How about it?
replace the table that kid messed up
What's wrong?
With this rule
For 10 turns each, 8 players surround the table
If there's one weak point in our defense
it will play havoc with the team
And from the perspective of the West team
I'm the only weakness
I'm a laughing stock
Hiroyuki
Go lightly
hunh?
Right now you're probably thinking you should try extra hard
but if you think that way you've already...
fallen into a trap
caught by the west team's strategy
What's being tested now
among your qualities
ISN'T your determination to win
Just simply
in a normal way
play as you always do
keep presence of mind
and don't lose sight of...
yourself
First Game
East Round 1
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 25000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 25000
West Team
Harada: 25000 Mitsui: 25000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
We're under rule that wins beneath Mangan don't count
so everyone is aiming for a Mangan win or greater
You'd think this would make for a spectacular game, but it doesn't
When someone feels their opponent has a big hand
they just abruptly take a cheap hand
Tsumo
Red Dragon only
and the rule that prevents accumulated wins
hangs heavy over us
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 25000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 25000
West Team
Harada: 25000 Mitsui: 25000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
Game 1
East Round 4
Of course, Mangan or greater hands...
they're easy to read based on related yaku
Additionally, as a Tsumo will decrease a teammate's points
there isn't really much point
But it's not easy to get a direct hit on the West Team players, either
A Man tile Chiniisou is a Haneman win
If I get it to Ikkitsuukan, that could go up to a Baiman win
If they suspect I have a Chiniisou
these players won't discard a single Man tile
Carefully, without attracting attention
SILENTLY
this is IDEAL
Chii
Harada's ready to go out.
A Pinzu one suit hand
I can't possibly discard this
Pon
Fuck.
He wasn't ready to go out after all
If not for this 5Pin, I'd have a 5 sided Man wait!
But for that it would be the best possible tenpai!
He may be Akagi, but tiles that won't pass will simply not pass
In the end my hesitation...
ruined the Chiniisou
Ron
Pinfu, Iitsu, one dora.
A Mangan win.
Because you were held captive by that Chiniisou, you could only see the 5Pin as "baggage"
After getting a good starting hand you thought it was TOO good
It's a tough game.
So be tough
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 25000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 25000
West Team
Harada: 25000 Mitsui:  17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
South Round 2
Ron
TanYao, 3 Dora
Mangan
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 17000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 25000
West Team
Harada: 25000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
South Round 4
Ron
Honitsu via South Wind
Mangan
[feels like shit]
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 9000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 25000
West Team
Harada: 25000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
Game 2
East Round 1
Tsumo
Chiniisou
Mangan
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 23000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
Game 2
East Round 4
We've been at the Mahjong Tag Team Match for 2 and a half hours
As I thought, Hiroyuki is the first one they'd try to corner
He's only got 7,000 points left
If he deals into a Mangan or greater hand
it's OVER
the result: he's paralyzed into playing defensively
Hiroyuki alone won't do it
endure enough to pass the hand to your partner, Akagi
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 23000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
2nd Game
East Round 2
So, the telltale signs of a Kokusi Musou, hunh?
Riichi
That riichi. Like intentionally throwing yourself off a cliff
If he discards a White dragon
he's dead!
At one stroke another of the East team eliminated
Kan
The fourth White Dragon?
My Kokusi Musou win just vanished
Christ. This is going nowhere
Ron
Riichi. Green Dragon. Three dora.
A south wind wait?
This guy knew to aim for my Kokusi Musou
and what's more, he did it with that shitty single tile wait riichi
Inconceivable!
Is he using Ganpai?
Ganpai: (lit: wounded tile) The cheat of marking tiles
that 7 Pin Kan
revealed the 4th White Dragon as dora indicator
and the South Wind I drew
You HAD to know all of these three things
otherwise that style of play isn't possible
SHIT
I'll beat that conceited fuck
If we replace all the tiles it's proof against Ganpai
But that just limits the cheat to one game at a time
His uncanny "luck" will just show itself again
I've got to uncover how he's doing it
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
Game 3
East Round 3
One tile from a SuuAnKou tenpai?
Ron
chitoitsu
a 1,600 point chitoitsu
clearly he won simply to prevent me completing my SuAnKou
But when he revealed his hand I caught a glimpse of something
While aiming for chitoitsu he discarded two pairs. Clearly a mistake
If all the tiles were marked, he ought to have been able to win sooner!
that is to say...
Ginji's marked tiles ring hollow
They must be very limited in scope
It's merely a stubborn threat
all bark, no bite
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
4th Game
South Round 1
Riichi
He played a safe pair
that's not how someone plays when they know my hand through gampai
As I thought
Ginji's marked tiles are almost entirely a bluff
Riichi
He's declaring Riichi NOW?
There's only one tile left to draw
Just Harada's "Haitei" draw.
Haitei: (lit. sea bottom) The final draw which offers additional points if used to win
Kan
and with that this hand is a draw
I don't want to see you getting any fucking riichi ippatsu Haitei win
just in case
waiting on a single West Wind
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS WIZARDRY?!?
Not a single flaw or mark
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
4th Game
South Round 4
What time is it?
It's been 7 hours since we started?
Okay
Break time
We start again
East Team
Ten: 25000 Hiroyuki: 7000
Akagi: 25000 Ginji: 21000
West Team
Harada: 15000 Mitsui: 17000
Soga: 25000 Nakatsu: 25000
Game 5
South Round 2
If I discard the South Wind I've got a pair wait on Red or White dragon
If I Riichi and Tsumo with a Tatehon
Tatehon: a closed Honiitsu (single suit) hand
this might go to a SanAnKou with Yakuhai-- a Baiman win
furthermore
my next draw is a White Dragon
no mistake
Riichi
With this... a BAIMAN win
It's not a White Dragon!
I'm certain on this tile's right side I...
Finally I've caught...
Ginji by his tail
In the end Ginji has only marked 7 tiles
only Honor tiles
Normally, it's done on the backs of tiles
But Ginji
while fiddling his tiles he smeared them with something
perhaps when he did that thing, touching his hair
He had rigged something for that moment
and he smeared it on the FACE of each tile
such that when the tiles are stacked
they'll stick up slightly
doing it to merely 7 tiles
it's like a pure and simple indicator
And now that defenseless back of yours
I'll cut it through
I'm done
Agreed
East Wind, SanAnKou, Chanta 4 Dora
A baiman win
A dealer baiman is 24,000 points!
Ginji is OUT
There is no second chance to stab through an enemy's defences
there is only the first swing of the blade
kill with the first cut
this is how it's done
Asai Ginji: Disqualified
YOU FUCK!